个人原创
严禁剽窃
翻译/校对/时间轴:JokerChou
片中一些内容真实发生过
1978年4月28日
纽约 广场酒店
你干什么 在背后捣鬼
What are you doing?Going behind my back
说我搞砸了这次行动
Telling people i'm screwing up this operation?
我他妈还给你订了间豪华套房
I got you a suite at The fucking Plaza Hotel
房间真烂 - 什么
The shittiest suite - What
真他妈烂
The shittiest fucking suite
为什么 - 东西太难吃
Based on what? - The food is wrong
这是什么 从我衣柜里拿的
And  What is this?- You got like one of my closet or something
不是 - 你帮他打扮的
No - Are you dressing him  like you're dressing me?
不 你想多了 这跟你没关系
No  what are you thinking?This is not about you
你想把我打扮得和他一样吗 像吗
Are you trying to dress me so that I look like him?
不 你们俩穿的不一样
No  you're not dressed like him
我看起来很像他 - 没有
I do look  I look like him  - No
他穿的是天鹅绒
He's in like velvet
你想知道事情是怎么完成的
You asked me to show you  how this is done
你要想搞砸的话 随你便
You wanna fuck it up  be my guest
听着 我从来没碰过她
Look  i never laid a hand on her  Alright?
就因为这个
Is that what  this is about?
严格说来 并不是
Technically  that's not true
我们没上过床好吧 我只是
Look  we never had sex okay?I just wouldn't do
我只是像这样把手放在
What will I do  I put my hand like this
他妈的别摸我
Don't you fucking touch me
你惹到我了
That  bothers me
哦 是吗- 是的
Oh  it does?- Oh  yeah
惹到你了- 对
That bothers you? - Yes
我也被一堆破事搞的心烦
You know  a lot of shit bothers me too
要是想惹你的话
But  i was just trying to help you If I wanted to bother you
我他妈的如果真想惹你
If I really wanted to fucking bother you?
就会这样
This is what I'd do
这才叫惹毛你
If I try to bother  that's what i would do
你不该这么做
You shouldn't have done that
怎么样 惹到你了吗
How's that  you bothered now?
好吧 别小题大做
Alright  don't make a thing of it
你不该碰他 他不喜欢这样
You shouldn't have touched him He doesn't like that
天 帮他把头发弄好
Oh  my God! Fix his hair  Jesus Christ!
得花点时间 好吧 这不像是
it takes some time  okay  It's not like just
我们得进去了 快点
We gotta get in the other room Come on
市长已经到了 - 我知道
The Mayor is in there - Yes  I know that
要不要去趟美容院
Should we go to the beauty parlour?Is that what we should do?
看起来怎么样
How does it look?
挺好
Fine
出发
Let's go
美国骗局
翻译/校对/时间轴:JokerChow
大家面对面坐下来 这种方式
This is face to face  person to person
人们都说我过时了
This is why call me old fashion  but
哎 不好意思
Hey  what?Excuse me  excuse me
由我替市长处理
I'll handle that for The Mayor
这是为市长准备的
Well it's for The Mayor
如果市长不接受 就是对酋长的不尊重
It'd be a sign of disrespect to the Sheikh If The Mayor didn't take it
这是为你准备的 市长
This is for you Mayor
怎么回事 卡尔 搞什么名堂
What're doing?Carl   what the fuck? What is this?
我会处理好 没事的 一切都在掌握之中
I'll take care of it  Everything's good I got everything under control
这是干什么- 我不知道
What is this?- I don't know  I don't know
莫名其妙
I don't know you
我不知道你们搞什么玩意 太奇怪了 知道吗
I don't know what the fuck  that is But  it's weird  You understand?
误会 误会
A misunderstanding Misunderstanding
我来这里是见酋长的 就这样
Look  I came here to meet a Sheikh That's all i know
我对此很有兴趣 但显然他没有来
I'm very interested in that He's not here  apparently
我有意要见这位酋长
I'm very interested in meeting The Sheikh
可却被放鸽子
You let me know when I get that
谢谢 祝你们愉快
Thank you  have a good day!
欧文
Irving
你最好把他叫回来
you better go and get him
赶紧叫他回来
Go out there and get him right now
我本来就不想干
I don't wanna do this in the first place
这是你大显身手的时候
This is your show
你去叫- 你没得选
you go get him - Look  you have no choice
把他弄回来 快去
You have to go get him Now  go get him
让他亲自收下手提箱
So  he takes the briefcase by himself
整个计划就是这样 欧文
That's the whole plan  Irving
看你干的好事 迫不及待地塞钱 蠢货
What were you doing pushing the fucking briefcase  dummy?
嗯
Huh?
你知道我花了多少钱
You know how much this fucking cost?
你他妈还要住豪华酒店
With this goddamn hotel that you fucking asked for
好 我现在给你收拾烂摊子
Now  I gotta go  mop up your mess
你搞的烂摊子 让我收拾
I'm gonna go fucking mop up your mess!
你明白吗 那样不行
Do you understand that he has...It wasn't working
他对酋长很失望
he was upset about the Sheikh
你有没有想方设法生存的经历
Did you ever had to find a way to survive?
尽管知道自己的选择很差劲
And you know  your choices were bad
当我还是个孩子时
I learned how to survive
我就学会如何生存
When I was a kid
我父亲以前做玻璃生意
My father  had a glass business
我宁可剥削别人也不愿被人剥削
I would rather be on the taking side then the getting taken side
每当看到父亲被人剥削
any day of the week Specially  after I saw my father get taken
我都感到十分恐惧不安
I mean  seeing that Scarred me for life
于是我自告奋勇去拓展业务
I took it upon myself to  drum up business
我变成和父亲完全不同的人
I became a different kinda then my father
成了一个职业骗子
I became a Con artist For real
彻头彻尾的
From the feet up
不管怎样
I was gonna survive
我都要生存下去
no matter what
我仍做着玻璃生意
I still had the glass business
还开了几家干洗店
And  a few dry cleaning stores also
兼职卖画
And i did  some art dealing on the side
赃物和赝品
Stolen or forged art
我是主人 大家玩的开心
I'm your host  enjoy  Enjoy!
某年一月 我去参加朋友的泳池派对
So  I go to my friends' pool party
在长岛
in Long Island
你手链上的照片是埃林顿公爵吗
Is that Duke Ellington on your bracelet?
是啊 他今年去世了 你知道吗
Yeah as a matter of fact it is He died this year  you know?
我知道 我猜这里
I know I doubt anyone else here
没人关心这个
knows or cares about it
我在乎 我的人生被他拯救了
Well  i care about it He saved my life many times
我也一样 哪一首歌
Mine too  Which one?
吉普布鲁斯
Jeep's Blues
Jeep's Blues?
嗯 吉普布鲁斯
mmhmm Jeep's Blues
你想听吗- 现在
You wanna hear it?- Right now?
对- 好的
Yeah - Sure
谁能演绎出这样的音乐
Who starts a song like that?!
太美妙了
It's magic
真美妙
Magic
他无需有一副好身材
He wasn't necessary in good shape
为人温和又有内涵
and he has this calm over
That was rather elaborate
他很有风度
He had this air about him
他的自信 让我着迷
And  he had this confidence
that drew me to him
他在做自己
He was  who he was
什么都不在乎
He didn't care
我觉得她是个很特别的人
I mean  she was a very particular person
像我一样
Like me
她来自一个没有太多选择的地方
she come from a place where her options were limited
有时确实会让人觉得性感
It actually can feel kind of sexy  sometimes
心中燃起一股勇气
There was a boldness in it
可是勇气会把我带向何方
But  where would that boldness take me?
我不知道
I didn't know
但我会找到答案的
But  I was gonna find out
像我一样
Like me
她学习生存和重塑自我
she learned to survive and reinvent herself
她明白必须重塑自己的人生
She knew she had to reinvent her life and her identity
和我一样 她为自己设想了一个
Like me  she envisioned a better
更美好的未来
elegant future for herself
和我一样 她得有个愿景
Like me  she knew she had to have a vision
她去了纽约
She came to New York;
满怀憧憬 就这样
She visioned it And  just like that
她到时尚杂志找工作
She applied for a job At the Cosmopolitan Megazine
显然你来这里有自己的想法 谈谈吧
You're obviously here for a reason let's get to it
我们现在的封面故事是为女性口交
Our cover story right now is on Cunnilingus
你对此怎么看
What do you think about that?
我挺喜欢
I like it
做过文秘吗 会不会打字
Do you have any clerical skills?Can you type?
她很与众不同
She was unlike anybody I ever knew
她很聪明
She was smart.
能看透别人
She saw through people in situations.
她懂得如何充满热情和品位地活着
and she knew how to live with passion and style
她懂埃林顿公爵
She understood Duke Ellington.
我身无分文
I was broke
无所畏惧
fearless
再无可失
Got nothing to loose
我的梦想比什么都重要
And my dream  more than anything
我要成为别人 而不是我自己
was to become anyone else other than who I was
他经营干洗连锁店
He had a chain of Dry cleaning stores
我在布朗克斯有两家
I got two in the Bronx
曼哈顿有三家
and uh three in Manhattan
嗨  拜伦
Hey  Byron
最近怎么样 这是西德妮
How're you doing? This is Sydney
他告诉我 如果需要衣服他这里有很多
He asked me  If I wanted to come in and upgrade my wardrobe
很多漂亮的衣服
He said he had a lot of nice things
顾客遗忘在这很久
That got left behind by people then forgot over the years
你都不会相信
Hey  you wouldn't believe the shit
客人落下了那么多东西
that people leave behind here
难以置信
They're unbelievable
顾客把东西落这儿了
People leave stuff here?
是啊 他们夜里出门
Oh  yeah They got out for the night
喝个烂醉
You know  they drink
第二天醒来
Come in the morning
把衣服扔这儿洗就忘得一干二净
put their clothes in and they forget
看看这 漂不漂亮
Is that nice or not?
有些衣服都放这儿好几年了
Some of these almost had been for years
他们不要 有人要
They are not picking it up
Someone's to pick it up
喜欢吗 - 好喜欢
Do you like it? - I love it
西德妮  这是你的了
Sydney  it's yours
你想要就拿去
You want it  it's yours
喔 我喜欢
Whooo  I like it
你看上去美极了
You look fantastic!
我的天
My God!
这是我梦寐以求的 太漂亮了
I can only dream about it These dresses are beautiful
这件 很好看
This  No  it's beautiful
快穿上看看
Put it on  come on
瞧瞧这
Look at that  Please?
真的吗
Really?
我感觉到有个秘密
I felt like we had a secret
只存在于我两之间
Just the two of us
当你只想和
You know  like that thing
when you just wanna be with
某个人在一起时
the one person all the time
你感觉到全世界只有你们两人能理解彼此
You feel like just the two of youunderstand that nobody else gets
我可以
I could just
向她坦白我的一切
tell her everything about myself
生命中从没有过像她这样的人
And  I never had anybody like that in my life before
那仿佛 我终于能真正做自己了
It felt like  finally I can truly be myself
丝毫不觉得丢脸 也不觉尴尬
Without being ashamed without being embaressed
这是什么地方
What is this place?
你在这里卖画
Do you sell lies here?
嗯 有时候 这是我的办公室
Yeah  sometimes  It's my office
我知道是办公室 可是
I know it's your office But
你在别的地方也有办公室
you have all these other places
这间是干吗用的
So  what's this for?
为什么带我来这儿
Why did you bring me here?
我要在这发展我的主业
This is getting to be my uh  my main business
我未来的生意
My going business
我放贷给那些贷不到款的人
I hold that loans to guys who can't get loans
就像他们的救命稻草
You know  like their last resort
救命稻草
You're their last resort
利率已经远超12%快飙到18%了
Since  interest rates are north to 12% and heading to 18%
懂的真多
That's nice smarty pants
该死的吉米卡特
Fucking Jimmy Carter
该死的尼克松
Fucking Nixon really
战争和财政赤字 所有这些操蛋玩意
The war and the defecit  and all that shit
爱死你了 你真聪明
I fucking love it you're so smart
太聪明了
You are
谢谢你 但是你怎么帮他们弄到钱
Thanks Kid  But  how do you get them the money?
嗯...- 弄不到 是吗
Well   - You don't  do you?
弄不到
You don't
这些家伙都不是什么好东西
Thes  these guys are lousy risks You know?
没法给他们贷款
I can't get them the loan
但我能拿到五千块酬劳
But I get my fee  five thousand
五千块
Five thousand?
你白拿走五千块 却什么都不给他们
You take five thousand and you don't get them anything
这些人都是坏蛋
These are bad guys  you know?
离过几次婚 嗜赌 贪污
They get pair of divorces gambling habits embezzling
都是些人渣
and all that shit
那些处在人生中的低谷
Everybody at the bottom crosses path eventually
在绝望中挣扎的人
In a  pool of desperation and
都是你的猎物
you are waiting for them
我们一起干怎么样
How about we?
我们 - 嗯
We? - mmhmm
怎么样
How about it?
西德妮 西德妮
Sydney? Sydney
对不起我说的太过分了
I'm sorry That was too much  i went too far
我不想让你难过
I didn't wanna upset you
西德妮 拜托 我错了
Sydney please I'm sorry!
我知道不是所有人都适合这行
I know it ain't for everybody
认识你真是太好了
Oh  God! I love getting to know you!
为什么要告诉她真相
Why did you have to tell the truth?Telling the truth?
为什么要这么做
Why did you do that for?
我不该告诉她真相
I should've never tell the woman the truth
可是她太聪明了 太与众不同了
But  she's so smart She is terrific
太与众不同了
She is terrific
天哪
God!
你说过 很高兴认识我
You said  it was nice knowing me
你说过 很高兴了解我
You said  it was nice to meet me
- 是啊
- Yeah
你想见见
Would you like  to meet
伊迪丝·格林斯雷夫人吗
Lady Edith Greensley
我在伦敦有皇家银行的业务关系
I have royal banking connections  in London
我很乐意帮你贷款 但是
I'd love to help you with loans But  of course
我挑选客户可是很严格的
I have to be verySelective
太他妈的精彩了
That was fucking fantastic
谢谢 喜欢吗- 当然喜欢
Thank you  Did you like it?- I liked it
谢谢你回来
Thank you for coming back
谢谢老天你回来了
Thank God you came back
我哪里都不去
I wasn't going anywhere
我爱死你了
I fucking love you
我是你的了
You have me
欧文和我开始合作
And  so   Irving and I began our partnership
爱情和商业共同合作
In love and commerce
丽贝卡
Rebecca
等一下
hold on
你是伊迪丝吗- 他让我向我朋友透露
You're Edith right?- He told me to tell my friends
我在伦敦银行有关系
I had London Banking connections
她跟我说  你能帮我弄到免抵押贷款
She told me  you'd get me a line of credit
我知道你在伦敦有业务关系
I know you have banking connections in London  England
然后拒绝对方
And  after that say 'No'
很多次
A lot
直到对方上钩
Until  the guy is hooked
听着 告诉她
listen  tell her
我从未错过任何一笔账单
I've never missed a check
简直很可怕
It was almost scary
从绝望的人手中骗到钱 是那么轻松
how easy it is to take money from desperate people
伊迪丝·格林斯雷夫人
Lady Edith Greensley
很高兴见到你 肯
It's so good to see you  Ken
夫人 尊贵的夫人
Lady  Your Ladyship
再次感谢
Thank you  again
规矩是这样的
These are the roles we were meant to play
我们的筛选条件非常严格
We are very selective
申请不够有说服力 我们谈过
Without strong application We talked about it
无法成交
I don't take a deal that i can't close
你不够积极
You're not being aggressive enough
如果你去过皇后区 去过大颈镇
If you've ever been to great neck
人人都知道我是经销商
Everybody knows my dealership
给你五千 帮我贷五万 对吧
Five thousand gets me fifty  right?
五千贷五万 没错吧
Five grands get me fifty?
我们一起做成的生意翻了两番 三番
I was doing so much more business with her We doubled  we tripled!
我从没见过任何一个人
I've never met anyone Men or Women;
在生意上如此谨慎和细致
In business Who's so careful and precise about
每一个细节都无懈可击
everything!Every stylishtic details
祝贺你 - 我们也一起卖画
Congratulations!- We kept selling art together too
这幅是《男孩和狗》 非宗教画
Its 'A Boy and His Dog' It's a non-religious painting
55年 黄金时代 荷兰画
深入往下谈以前我想问 这画合法吗
Before we go any further Is this legit?
这么说吧 这幅是在西班牙丢失的
Ah  let's just say  you know it's missing from Spain
就这样
Let's leave at that
别给西班牙朋友看到
Don't show it to any Spanish friends
事业开始飞黄腾达
I mean  it just took off!
我们换了更好的办公室
We got a better office
取名伦敦联合公司
We called it  London Associates
在她身边我感到很快乐
When I was around her I felt 'joy'
真他妈快乐
Fucking Joy!
还有爱
And  love
这就是我的感觉
That's what i felt
在我看来
As  as far as I can see
人们总是在尔虞我诈
People are always conning each other
为了一己私利
To get what they wanted
甚至连自己都骗
We even 'Con' ourselves
我们说服自己
We talk ourselves into things
购买东西
We sell ourselves things
不管需要与否
whether we do need or want
我们粉饰谎言
You know  we are dressing 'em up
不顾及风险
We leave out the risk
对丑陋的事实视而不见
We leave out the ugly truth
留意一下
Pay attention to that
我们总是用各种方式欺骗自己
Cos  we are always conning ourselves in one way or another
只是为了活下去
Just to get through life
他结过婚
He was married
还有个儿子
and he had a son
爸爸
Daddy!
他过继了妻子的孩子
He had adopted her son
是个很好的好爸爸
He's a really good dad
对此我很敬佩他
I respected him  for that
这事对任何人来说都不容易
It was a tough situation for everyone
你今天干嘛了
What did you do today?
多诺万小朋友对我很凶
That kid Donovan is being mean to me
那个大孩子 但是 他…
That big kid?But he
妈妈接你回家 他没机会烦你
Mommy was picking you up So  he couldn't bother you
她去迟了
She was late
后来我们把火扑灭了 妈妈说
And then  after we put out the fire Mommy said
让我待屋里玩棒球卡
to stay in my room with my baseball cards
等等 什么火
What fire?
你知道吗他们发明了一种叫太阳的灯
Did you know they made a lamp that had the sun in it?
妈妈买了那个灯
Mommy got the lamp
她做饮料的时候 灯着火了
She made a special drink and the lamp made a fire
我把火扑灭了
I put out the fire
灭了
The fire is out!
这是我一生做的最正确的事
First time in my life  I do the right thing
闭嘴
Oh  shut up!
拯救了一个年轻的单身妈妈
Save  a young single mother
和一个孩子
and a kid
我娶了你 认了孩子 - 你爱上我了
I married you  I adopt him - You fell in love
你敢把这茬忘了 我们当年可是疯狂的相爱
Don't you dare forget that part We fell madly in love!
是的 相爱 我的天 是的
Yes  I fell in love My God  I fell   yes
我原以为你有种神秘感 像我妈一样
What I thought you were mysterious like my mother
后来发现 所谓的神秘感不过是消沉而已
Until it turned out the mysterious just meant depressed
Alright?
让人难以亲近
Hard to reach
我都快憋死了
I mean  i'm dying here!
你应该找个好男人
You need somebody who's gonna be quiet
你那么年轻漂亮
You're young  you're beautiful
应该结识其他人
You gotta find somebody else you gotta
出门交朋友什么的 - 我不喜欢出去
go out and get some friends  Alright?- I don't like going out
你又不是不知道我一见人就焦虑
You know that I get anxiety when i get to meet people
你知道这对我来说多困难
You know how hard that is
可你不能总待家里玩日光灯
You cannot just stay in the house with a fucking sunlamp!
好吗 我不能
Alright? I can't  I mean look
我很不放心你带丹尼 尤其当你
I can't trust you with Danny When you're
着火什么的
the fire and everything
我把火弄灭了 欧文 又没出什么事
I put the fire out Irving There's no fire
也许 如果你经常回家
Maybe if you were here more
压根就不会起火
Then there wouldn't have been a fire in the first place
我要是在就不会起火
There wouldn't have been a fire
if i was here?
别再提火的事了
Just stop with the whole fire thing!
只是个意外
God! It was a mistake
很多人都会遇到
I'm sure million people do that
日光灯一直都很危险
All the time
Those sunlamps are dangerous
我真不该把它放家里
I shouldn't have it in the house  really
我打赌这种事经常发生
I bet that happens all the time
没什么大不了的
This was nothing
我们在一起不开心 知道吗
We are not happy  alright?
你知道我会把丹尼带走
You know that I could take Danny
你干的工作大多都不合法
You know that most your work is illegal
你要是想跟我离婚
And  you know that if you try to divorce me
我不是说我想带走丹尼
i'm not saying that I would
但我可以那么做
But  i'm saying that I could
这就是我不想离婚的原因 欧文
But  i'm saying that
That is why  I don't like divorce Irving
女人离了婚
Women do that in divorces
母亲抚养孩子父亲永远也别想见
Women get the children and the father never gets to see them
我妈没离过婚
My mother never got divorce
我祖母也没离过婚
My granmother never got divorce
我们家族没有离婚史
There are no divorces in my family
我也绝不会离
I am not  getting a divorce
算了吧 我们这是干嘛
Come on  what are we doing here?
床头吵架床尾和 我们不就这样吗
We fight and we fuck And  that's what we do
一直都是啊
That's our thing!
她深谙以守为攻的艺术
She's the Picasso of Passive agressive karate
她比我认识的任何一个骗子都厉害
She was better than any con artist they ever met
包括我自己 我真的拿她无可奈何
Including myself And  she had me like nobody had me
欧文 他妈的给我过来 快点
Irving come the fuck up Come on
你可能会说
You might say
这就是我当骗子的因果报应
she was my Karma For how i took advantage of people
哦 老天 - 过来
Oh  my God!- Come here
来 到床上来
Come on  get in the bed
别 等等 - 宝贝 有好东西让你瞧瞧
No  wait - Baby  there's such good stuff here
我不能丢下孩子不管
I did not wanna leave kid behind
他是我儿子
He's my son!
她控制了我 我是她手中的筹码
She had me I  was her mark
我现在不能向你保证
Now  I can't assure you
贷款一定能批下来
That your loan will be approved
但我得提醒你
But  I can tell you that
一旦拍板
any deal I take  I close
费用恕不退还
However my fee is not refundable
就像时间不能倒转一样
Just like my time
非常感谢你能见我 欧文
I wanna thank you very much Irving  for seeing me
对不起 我太紧张了
Sorry  i'm so nervous
是不是没扣扣子
Is that  am I not buttoned?
罗森菲尔德先生 我只想说
I just gotta say Mr Rosenfeld that
伊迪丝夫人
Lady Edith was uh
业务水平一流
very you're top notch and
我十分需要你们的帮助 我已经绝望了
I really need your help I am desperate
我有奥迪车 还有两艘船
I mean I got the Audis and two boats
忘了说一点
I forgot to mention
我在长岛还有块地产
that I have a little piece of real estate in Long Island
嗯 没听你提过
Hmm  you didn't mention that
跟你吃过两顿午饭都没听说过
Two lunch with you you never mentioned that
我本来正准备说
Oh  I was gonna mention it
有个戴帽子的家伙走进来
Then the guy with the hat walked in
戴帽子的 - 你记得吗  - 记得
The hat - You remember that?  - I do
第二次吃饭的时候 - 对
That second time we had lunch - Yes
都看不到他的眼睛 好像没眼睛一样
We couldn't see his eyes Like he had no eyes
有卖那种帽子的吗 - 不知道
Did they sell hats like that?- I don't know
我去商店时
Actually  i went down the store
还想去帽子店看看
and i thought the hat store down the street
打算买一顶那样的送你
I thought  I was gonna get you one as like
就当是个纪念品 - 吃了两次饭
It was like a momento - Two lunches?
是的
Yes
真的
Really?
两顿饭而已 有什么大不了的
It's two lunches  What's the big deal
不寻常啊
That's unusual
只想让他变得积极一点
Just trying to get him to be more agressive
在他的贷款问题上
On his loan  that is
你带我发现了这个城市崭新的一面
You showed me whole new side of the city
我以前从未见过
I've never seen before
不客气 - 谢谢你
You're welcome - No  thank you
我能请你吃饭吗?
Yeah  Should I take Edith?
你喜欢吧 - 是的
You'd like it - Yes
我要请两次
So  I'll take you there twice
得了吧
Stop
你喜欢这家伙 - 喜欢
You like this guy?- Yes  I like this guy
干扰了你的判断吗
Is this messing with your judgment?
当然不会 别傻了
No,it's not messing with my judgment.Don't be stupid.
做好你的本分 -好 你也一样
Fine  you play your part
务必帮我转达给你们英国的同事
Take it to your people  in London
拜托了 转达一下
Please Take it to them
我支票都带来了
I got the cashier's check right here
五千贷五万对吧
I give you five and you give me
fifty back  right?
求你们了
Please
别拒绝我
Please  don't reject me
给我个机会吧
Give a guy  a chance
你在苏黎世有办公室
Zurich  you got office in Zurich?
还是巴黎 - 等我们一下
Paris  I can call Paris? Give me a sec
没问题 你们忙吧
Do whatever you need to do
没事 慢慢来
Go ahead  take your time
留在这别走
Stick around for a little bit
看到我那边的同事了吗
See my friends over there?
你们走错地了
You got the wrong office
你们马上会很尴尬
You're gonna be embarrassed
嗨 嗨 嗨 对她温和点
Hey  hey  hey  hey!Go easy on her
我没逮住你的死手 欧文
I may not have you Irving
但我们有她诈骗的证据
But I have her on fraud
冒充他人
Impersonating another individual
诈骗
On fraud
身份欺诈?
What is that? Identity fraud?
你也许是从英国来
You may be from England
但你不是皇室成员
but you're not royal
也没有任何银行背景
and you have no banking connections
这可是重罪
That's a felony
得判三到五年
How long is it?That's three to five years
哦 是吗真有趣
Oh  really?That's interesting
我连你名字都不知道
I don't even know your name
里奇·迪马索  FBI 很高兴见到你
Richie DiMaso  F B I
Nice to meet you
你该离这家伙远一点
You gotta keep away from this guy
三天了 警察都不让我见她
He wouldn't let me see her  for three days
甚至还设法推迟律师
Even managed to delay a lawyer
她承受不了了
She couldn't handle it
查克 荧光灯怎么开着呢
Chuck  how come the fluorescence is on?
关了行吗
Can we kill that please?
我放了个台灯给你
Jesus Christ  i put this lamp here for you
对你可能有好处 但是他们不放心电线
Cos i thought it will be better for you
This wires here
有人会用电线上吊
They're scared b'cos people hang themselves
可我知道 你那么聪明不会做傻事的
But  i know  you're too smart for that
桌子椅子跑哪去了 连床都没有
Where is the table and chair?
这简直就是个他妈的收容所
It's like a fucking asylum
乔 今天大家都放假吗
Joe is everybody off today?
上帝啊 真可怕
Jesus Christ!It's scary
也许我就是想吓唬你 我也不清楚
Maybe  i wanted to scare you I don't know
也许就是我的主意
Maybe  i'm little
我有点离经叛道
off the beaten path,You know?
不晓得 也许吧
I don't know  maybe
你看样子有点脱水
You look dehydrated
喝茶吗
You wanna have some tea?
我知道你以为 嗨 看着我
I know you think  look at me Hey
伊迪丝 我知道你以为欧文很爱你
Edith  I know you think Irving loves you
我知道你认为
I know you thinking that uhm
他眼中的这个世界
You think that he sees the world
就如同这个黑暗冰冷的地方
as this a cold dark place
他对谁都漠不关心
He cares about nobody
除了他名单上的极少数人
But are very few people in the short list
他孩子 父亲 老婆
His son father wife
你觉得你属于这极少数
You think you're in the list
但如果不是呢
What if you are not?
如果你不在他的名单之列呢
What if you are not on that list?
如果他根本就不在乎你呢
What if you're not onthat list  at all?
被关进来的本应该是他
He'd be in here right now If he took the check
可现在变成你了
But now you did
我看得太清楚了
God! It's so clear to me
再清楚不过
It's so crazy clear to me
只有你当局者迷 他在利用你 伊迪丝
But it's not clear to you He uses you  Edith
利用你保护自己 他儿子
To protect himself To protect his son
和他长岛的妻子
and his wife in long Island
就是如此
No? Yes!
他跟她结了婚 还认了她儿子
He put a ring on her finger He adopted her son
他们有座大房子 还有两辆车
They have huge house they have two cars
她整天在干嘛 我来告诉你
What does she do all day?I'll tell you what she does
摆弄指甲 看电视
She plays with her nail  she watches T V
花你的钱
and she spends your money
你挣来的钱
The money that you make
我不想你进监狱而他逍遥法外
I don't like that you're in jail While he is going free
我不愿看到这样的结果 我想帮你
I don't like any of that I wanna help you
他耍的那些花招
All the 'razzle-dazzle' that he does
都是假的 骗人的
is not good It's not real It's fake
你就是你自己
Who you are is who you are
在你和上帝之间
Between  you and God
你和你的灵魂之间
You and your soul
这才重要 这才有意义
That's what matters That's what counts
这才是我要说的
That's what i'm about
这才是我从你身上看见的
That's what I see in you
告诉我
Tell me
我们第一次见面时 难道你没感觉吗
you didn't feel
the first time we saw each other
我疯了吗 绝对不是
Am I crazy?I don't think so
我不该在这里说这些话的
I am not supposed to be talking about this
我不在乎违反规定
I don't care I break the rules
伊迪丝  伊迪丝 我想帮助你
Okay  Edith  Edith I wanna help you
我喜欢你
I like you
在这儿三天了
Been in here three days
她状态不太好啊
This doesn't look good for her
看着她被关里面有何感觉
How does it make you feel  her in there?
账本是你的 对吗
That check was for you  right?
但是有些东西不见了
But  you knew something was off
因为你很聪明
Because you're good
这个国家最顶尖的一类人
You're like the best of the whole country
不是吗
Aren't you?
如果国家由你这种人掌管
You know  if the country were run bypeople like you
欧文·罗森菲尔德
Irving Rosenfeld
我们这些人都会被绞死 就像在危地马拉
We're gonna be up stringing like Guatemala
你去过危地马拉吗
You ever been to Guatemala?
你想买个电话或公寓
If you ever tried to get a telephone or an apartment
都会被绞死
or anything in Guatemala
国家就会变成那样
That's what this country would be like
如果让你这种人掌权
If we let people like you run this country
谁给你的权利评判别人
Who made you God and Judge?
我姨妈活到93岁
My Aunt Gria lived to be 93 years old
一辈子没撒过谎
Never lied in her life
那恭喜你 - 谢谢
Congratulations!- Thank you
我也为此感到骄傲
I'm proud of that too
当一个好人
Except make you another good person
岂不是一件值得争取的事
Isn't that something to strive for?
为什么一直在挖苦我
Why are you breaking my balls  huh?
说重点
Get to the point
我看出你很有能力 欧文
I see something in you  Irving
我很激动
I get very excited
我觉得未来有很多可能
I think that we have a lot of potential here
听着
Now  look?
我有个想法
I came up with the idea
是我的事情 我想改变
It's all for me I wanna change things
我正在追踪白领犯罪
I wanna go after White collar crime
欧文  你在这方面很有技巧
Irving  you're a very skilled man
我想让你教会我
And I want you to teach me;
抓到四个像你这样的罪犯
Hell  we can do this I want four people to do what you do
假投资 假存款
Fraudulent investments Fake certificates of deposits
偷画 伪造艺术品
Stolen art  fake art
你协助我逮到四个
You get me four people
就可以脱身了
You're off the hook!
四个人
Four busts
你就放过我们了
And you will leave us alone?
不用作证吗
We don't have to testify?
只要你搞定 就了结了 你想怎样都可以
If you got it  you're done Anything you want
但你要是逃的话 这辈子就完蛋了
But  if you run  then your life is over
把你抓起来 下场会很惨
You're gonna be hunted You're gonna be very difficult
你老婆孩子也受牵连
for Rosalyn and the kid To live in this country
我们得离开这里
We need to leave
现在就走
We need to run and we need to do it now
爱沙尼亚也好 罗马尼亚也好
Right  we'll go to Estonia or Romania
不管了 带上现金立马走人
I don't care,take the cash in the bag get out of here
我都说一百遍了
We talked about it a hundred times!
丹尼怎么办
What about Danny?
什么丹尼怎么办
我认了他 他跟我姓
I adopted him I gave him my name
我不能把他留给罗莎琳
I'm not leaving him wih Rosalyn She's
她靠不住 - 罗莎琳在控制你
unstable!- That is a manipulation
她不会放手的
Rosalyn will never let you go
她拿丹尼做挡箭牌
She used Danny against you
因为她处境糟糕 根本离不开你
Because she's too messed up to let you leave
我不能丢下孩子 我爱他
I can't leave him I love him  alright?
他是我儿子
He is my son
里奇猜到你会这么说
Richie said  you will say that
里奇? - 对
Richie? - Yeah
那个警察-对
The cop? -Yeah
你们关系都熟到直呼其名了 - 没错
You're on a first name basis  what?- Yes  i am
我根本就不在你的名单上对吧 - 什么名单
I am not even on your list  am i?- What list?
你的初选名单 候选名单
Your list  Your short list   your long list
我在你心里没有任何地位
I'm not even on any of your fucking list
我原以为你爱我 - 我爱你
I thought that you love me - I love you
我以为我们心有灵犀
that we have something
当然了 我们在一起很完美
We do have something  It's perfect!
你怎么说的来着 去罗马尼亚
What are you saying?We're gonna go to Romania
是吗- 是的
Is that what you're saying?- Yes
我就是这么说的
Yes  that's what I am saying
你 我 还有丹尼 没错
You  Me  Danny Yes
你之前可没这么说
Well  you never said that before
我现在就拿定主意了
Well  i am saying it now
我们共同经历这场冒险 就像以前一样
We are us We can make it an adventure  like we did
一起挺过难关 好吗
We can make it an adventure like we make everything  alright?
好的 - 好吗?
Alright - Okay?
必须得离开 明白吗相信我
We have to go now  alright?Trust me
马上就动身
We have to leave right now
没拿到监护权我不能离开丹尼
I can't leave Danny  without custody
不 你必须带我走 必须走
- No  you have to take me away We have to leave
你什么意思 什么意思
No  what are you saying?What are you saying?!
你冷静一下
Will you pull it together
别说我不爱你 那是胡扯
Don't say I don't love you That is bullshit
胡扯
This is bullshit
我们都是垃圾
WE  are bullshit
你就是垃圾
You are bullshit
满嘴谎言
别这样
Please  don't do this
我没想到你会骗我
I just never thought that you're conning me
我没骗你啊
I can never con you
我爱你
I love you
别这样说了
Please don't say this
我完了
No  I am done
别这样说
Don't say that
我要搞定这四个骗子
I'm gonna do these four busts these four cons
把我们救出去
To get us out of this
不单为我自己 是为我们
Not just me  but us
而且我要接近
And  i'm gonna get really close
里奇 那个警察
with Richie The Cop
万一需要利用他
In case  we need to use him
留条后路
If we need another move
不会到那一步的
We won't need another move
抓到四个人
We need four busts
就能脱身了
Then we are done
我们需要留个后路
We are gonna need another move
相信我 你会感激我的
Trust me and you'll gonna be thanking me
关键在于人们相信什么
The key to people is what they believe
想相信什么
And  what they want to believe
我要相信我们彼此坦诚
So  I want to believe that we were real
彼此坦诚
We are real
我要相信那个男人渴望我
I want to believe that a man could want me
我要让他心碎得彻底
I'm gonna take all of that heartbreak and  all of that sorrow
我要利用他
I am going to use it
让他相信我也渴望他
And  i'm going to make Richie think
that I want him
喜欢他
and that I like him
我要做得让人信以为真
And  I'm gonna be  very  very convincing!
我很生你的气
And  I am pissed at you
很生你气
Cos I am pissed at you!
说不定我真的喜欢他
Maybe  I do like him
很喜欢他
Maybe I like him a lot
彻头彻尾 对吧
From the feet up  right?
宝贝
Baby?
想办法让我们摆脱困境
Quit  bellyaching and come up with something to get us out of this
你是对的 我无法应付这事
You're right  I am in no state to deal with this
就看你的了 智多星先生
So  what's it gonna be Mr Mastermind
阿拉伯酋长
An Arab Sheikh
要阿拉伯酋长做什么
What do we want an Arab Sheikh  for?
你以为呢傻瓜
What do you think this was  stupid?
别叫人家傻瓜
If you could not call him Stupid Which he isn't
他比你聪明多了
He is smarter than you
上回他掌控住了局面
Last time i checked  he's in control
现在我们为他工作 客气一点
and we work for him ,so be nice
设圈套
To set this up
才能逮住骗子
To bust the Con artist
用蜜罐
We need to make the honey pot
才能吸引蜜蜂
To attract the bees
为了吸引蜜蜂
我们要介绍给他们
we need to offer them
让他们有利可图的富人
wealthy individual That they can take advantage of
特殊的 新颖的 前所未见的人
Someone special  Someone new  someone amazing
假装贷款给他们
And  those guys that I wanna sell
fake bank sheets
就能引出我们要的人 明白了吗
leads to that guy take the Sheikh's money.You see?
不通过中间人 他们就见不到那笔钱
Only  they can't get into his money
Unless  they knew somone
我们就是中间人 - 很好
And  that someone is us - Oh  that's good!
要是想抓到某人 比如你那个骗子朋友
So if wanna get something like your con artist friend
卡尔·艾尔威
Carl Elway
你引他买或卖 - 小点声
You get him wanna buy or sell - Keep your voice down
卖赝品或赃物或假银行单
Sell fake art or stolen art or fake certificates of deposit.
他需要一个富豪酋长来买单
Who does he need? He needs a rich sheik guy.
这样就能一下子把他抓住
There you go  We can pinch him
对 但我不会主动找艾尔威
That's right But I don't tell Elway shit.
我要等他来找我
I wait for him to call me
骗子圈很小
The art world is a small world
艾尔威的一个熟人
And one of Elway's acquaintance
已经盯上我们了
is clocking us right now
哪儿 - 别看
Where? Don't look.
看清楚了吗
You have a good look?
你怎么认识酋长的
How do you know the Sheikh?
他是我朋友艾尔 来自皇后区
This is my friend Al  from Queens
我是做铝墙板和屋顶的
I do aluminium siding and roofing
给你看样东西
I wanna show you something
这幅伦勃朗的画
This Rembrandt here
世界各地的人都来参观
People come from all over the world to see this
不错
Yeah  he's good  Yeah
是赝品
It's a fake
不可能吧
But  it's impossible
人们相信他们想相信的东西
People believe  what they wanna believe
画这幅赝品的家伙
The guy who made this
非常厉害
was so good
对人们来说 这就是原作
That it's real To everybody
现在谁是大师
Now  who is the Master?
原作者
The Painter
还是伪造者
or the Forger?
这是假的
That's a fake?
世界就是这样运转
This is the way the world works
不是非黑即白
Not  black and white Like you were saying
而是极其的中庸
Extremely  grey
欧文 打扰一下
Irving  could I?
亚瑟 我跟你说过多少次了
How many time I gotta tell you
现在不能见酋长
You can't meet the sheik.
现在不行 不是时候 - 你好 亚瑟
Not yet  Wait your turn - Arthur  Hi
你好 我是伊迪丝
- Edith  Hi
我要跟你介绍一下罗伯特·斯潘塞
Yes  I wanted to introduce you to Robert Spencer
我们都是酋长的顾问
We are advising the Sheikh  together
我是罗伯特·斯潘塞  酋长的顾问
Robert Spencer  advisor to the Sheikh  Yeah
酋长是怎么回事
What's this about a goddamn Sheikh?
为什么没把我算在内
Why are you leaving me out of this?
我还是从朋友那听说的
Huh? I gotta hear it from my friends?
这不适合你 卡尔 - 什么意思 不适合我
It ain't for you  Carl - What do you mean  it ain't for me?
对 你不适合
No  it ain't for you
我给你做存单
We gotta do certificates of deposits
你要多少我给你印多少
I can print as many as you need
我已经找到合伙人了 都是合适的人选
I got my associates  it's the right guys
这事不是一个人能办到
C'mon  this is not one man operation
我能找到其他帮手
Look  I can get other guys
你说什么呢 欧文?
What are you talking about  Irving?
你能找齐四个人
you can get four guys
卖假银行单
To sell  fake certificate of deposits
给我的投资者 一周之内
To my investor  Within a week?
是的 我能做到
Yes  I can make that happen
只有想不到 没有做不到
Carl no way can do what he says he can do
有意思 但其他人都在门口等我
That's interesting But you know other guys lined up;
我要开会了
I gotta meeting
卡尔 他的合伙人到了
Carl  his associate says here
他要去开会了
He's got a meeting  he has gotta go to
我得走了 - 别走 别走
I gotta run - Listen  don't go   don't go
人是很奇怪的动物 你拒绝得越多
The crazy thing about people The more you say 'no'
他们越渴望得到
The more they want in on something
真愚蠢 - 我得走了
It is so stupid - I gotta run!
别着急 我会告诉他的
C'mon  I'll tell him  Don't worry  I'll tell him
你知道吗 卡尔刚才跟我说
Hey  you know what?Carl just told me
他能用四个人做完这一笔
He said we could do this whole thing with four guys
一周之内
within a week
我们还能干更大的
We could do something much bigger
更大的
Something bigger?
我的人签了几个亿美金
Yes  my guy deals with hundreds of million of dollars
你的多大- 几个亿
How much bigger?- Hundreds of million
我就知道你一直瞒着我 欧文
I knew you were holding out on me  Irving
几个亿真是够大的
Hundreds of million of dollars are much bigger
就像我说的
Like  i'm talking about
谁他妈也想不到
we can say never the fuck mind to see this
我们完全有可能干一票巨额的
And  we could have some complete access to something huge!
巨额 比如
Huge  like what?
我是罗伯特·斯潘塞 酋长的顾问
Robert Spencer  I'm advisor to the Sheikh
卡尔·艾尔威
Carl Elway
你想想
I want you to think
新泽西最被低估的价值是什么
the most under valued asset in the state of New Jersey
重建大西洋城啊
The rebuilding of Atlantic city
一年前赌博就合法化了
Look  maybe they legalized gambling a year ago
但现在没有任何动静
But nothing is happening
没有执照
No licenses
见好就收 卡尔
Hey  quit while you're ahead  Carl
我认识个人
I know the guy
他能帮你忙
the right people that are gonna help you out
谁- 他叫卡迈因·鲍里托
Who's the guy?- The guy is Carmine Polito
这人是谁
Who's Carmine Polito?
卡迈因·鲍里托?
Carmine Polito?
卡迈因·鲍里托  不行
Carmine Polito  No
我的上司斯托达德跟我说
My boss Stoddard proceeded to tell  me that
卡迈因·鲍里托
Carmine Polito was
是新泽西最有权力的人
the most quietly powerful person in the state of New Jersey
在种族混合的卡姆登市土生土长
A lifetime native of the very racially mixed Camden
那里已经变成了贫民窟
Which had become a ghetto
他当市长已经十年
And  where he had been Mayor for ten years
很受人们的热爱
A very beloved guy
他从没放弃过他的市民
A guy  who never gave up for his people
他父亲是意大利移民
His father had immigrated from Italy
是个司炉工
And  had stoked coal
有五个孩子的大家庭
A BIG family guy with five kids
有的孩子是收养的
They even adopted some other kid
那个黑人孩子是男孩女孩俱乐部的
a black kid from boys and girls club
老家在波士顿
from a Boston family
这是个犹太人家庭
I mean  his house hold was a Jewish place
他妻子多莉
And  his wife Dolly
是他眼中的珍宝
well she was the apple of his eye
也是家庭的中心
And  the centre of the household
每个人都喜欢这家伙
I mean everyone  love this guy
他有颗宽厚的心
And  he had a huge heart
公共事业振兴署聘用工匠画了这幅壁画
The W P A employed craftsmen to paint this
在大萧条时期
during the depression
如今我们也可以
Why can't we employ people  today?
像这样重建大西洋城
To do work like this and rebuilding Atlantic City?
他和所有的工会合作
He worked with all the unions
他是州众议院的领袖
He was the leader of the state assembly
他使新泽西赌博合法化 增加就业
And  he just got gambling legalized in New Jersey  to create jobs
可他筹不到钱重建大西洋城
But  he couldn't get the funds to rebuilt Atlantic City
这就是困扰他的问题
And that  was his problem
寻求不到帮助
So  with out help
他就在错误的时间把手伸向错误的地方
He was about to have his hand in the wrong pocket at the wrong time
在我看来 就是贪污
And to me  that meant corrupt
你说过目标是骗子
You said  grifters  con artists
而不是政客
We are not going after some politicians  This is
这个主意不好 里奇
This is a bad idea  Richie
很简单 你要做的
Look  it's really simple All you need
就是把两百万美金
is to put two million
打到账户上 - 什么
In a Chase account - What?!
存在酋长的名下
Under the Sheikh's name
谁的两百万美金
Whose  two million dollars?
听好了
Sh  just listen
两百万
Two miliion dollars
酋长的名下 一个账户
under the Sheikh's name
In a Chase account
一切都在掌控中
That will be controlled
当卡迈因
When Carmine
拿起电话打给银行
calls up on the telephone calls the bank
他会发现酋长确有其人
And  he sees that the Sheikh is real
账户也是真实的
And he has a real account
五天时间
Five days
我不能把纳税人的两百万
I'm not taking 2 million dollars of the tax payers money
放在任何地方五天
putting it anywhere for five days
我不管一切是否在我们的掌控中
I don't care  if we control it the whole time
放手让我们做
Start let us do  what we need to do
端掉腐败
To rule out corruption
揪出那些国家养着的蛀虫
And  to get rid of the pay-offs Guys that are ruining this country
这是我的梦想 别笑
That's my dream Don't smirk please
理查德 我理解你急切的心情
Richard I understand your eagerness
十分理解
I really do
我是密歇根人 你知道吧
You know  i'm from Michigan right?
跟你讲个故事
Let me tell you a story
关于我 父亲和哥哥的
About me and my dad  my brother
我们过去常在十一月去冰钓
We used to go  ice fishing every November
冰钓 所有人都盼望的事情
Ice fishing  that's all anybody that's what we live for
听我说
Just listen to me!
很美好 我们有个小火炉
It's beautiful! We had a little stove
大家围坐取暖
You huddle around We keep each other warm
把鱼钩丢下去 等着鱼上钩
You drop a line and you just wait
有一年我哥哥说 我们十月份就去吧
One year  my brother says  let's go on october
他想十月去冰钓
He wants to go ice fishing in October
爸爸就说 不行 冰面太薄
My Dad says no  the ice is too thin
我哥哥就说
My brother says
我懂了
I understand what that was
是不是你哥哥去了 冰太薄
Is that your brother went out on the ice the ice was too thin
他就掉下去 掉水里了
He fell through the ice Went into the water
因为他和我一样都太急切了
cos he was too eager  Just like i'm too eager
你想说的就是这个吗 - 不是
Is that what you're saying?- No  i'm not saying
那你说的是什么
What are you saying?
我们下次在谈冰钓的故事 年轻人
You know  we'll finish the ice story another time  young man
不要再提卡迈因·鲍里托了
For now  no Carmine Polito
回去工作吧
Go do your job
整件事被斯托达德否决了
Staunton shot the whole thing down
无聊
Boring
但是伊迪丝是个天才
But  Edith was a genius
她接触到掌管接线室的那个女人
She somehow  found this woman Who controlled the wire room
我听都没听说过这个人
A woman  I had never even heard of
长久以来 在单位里
Way back  in the dorm buried
in the bureau
这位猫女士连个说话的人都没有
This cat lady no one even talk to
伊迪丝在女洗手间认识了她
And  Edith met her in the ladies room
两人成了朋友
Yeah  became friends with her
嗨 你好吗
Hi  how are you?
所有的线路都由这位女士管
This lady handles all the wires
现在她和我们一起工作了
And now  she was working with us
她非常开心能参与到我们的行动中
She was excited  to be included in the operation
而不是被人遗忘
Instead of just being on the other end of a memo
这很好
It was beautiful
从英国带来的 - 对
This is from England?- yeah
我还给你带了些茶叶
Oh  I brought you some tea as well
太感谢了
Oh  thank you so much!
平时都没人和我说话 - 我知道
Nobody ever talks to me - I know
他们只对我说
They just say
"布兰达 埋头工作 别问问题"
Brenda  do the clerical wiring stuffs and don't ask questions
跟里奇说说你的猫
You need to tell Richie about your cats
他喜欢猫 -我的猫
He loves cats -My Cats?!
这是帕里 看他站起来的样子
Well  that's Perry Look at him  standin up
多可爱
Isn't that sweet?!
这是温迪 她很淘气
And  that's Wendy she's a rascal
伯纳比可不一样了
But  Bernaby  that's another story
他会弹钢琴
Bernaby plays the piano
好厉害
That's impressive
让她来转账
We got her to wire
两百万进了FBI控制的大通银行账户
2 million dollars to an FBI controlled account at Chase
钱将在帐上留五天
It'd be there for five days
如果鲍里托打电话确认
And  if Polito called?
他会知道酋长确有其人
He would see that the Sheikh was real
等到斯托达德反应过来时
And  by the time he Stauton caught up to us
我的绝妙点子会给他上司留下深刻印象
Edith made sure  his boss was impressed by my idea
他还什么都没搞明白时
So  before he even knew it was happening
上司已经打电话祝贺他了
His boss was calling to congratulate him
安东尼·阿玛多
Anthony Amado
他一心想让自己出名
He had a major hard on for to make a name for himself
这事让他出尽风头 这家伙一定快活死了
I mean this guys love the idea of being famous
斯托达德只能承认这全是我的主意
And  Stauton had to say it was all his own idea
还在他上司面前丢丑
or he'd look stupid in front of his boss
我莫名其妙被上司夸奖
You made me accept praise from my boss thanking me
而这事根本不该发生
for something that never should have happened
我压根就没批准 - 你应该高兴才对
Something that I didn't approve - You should be happy
你办公室出了件很有想象力的事
There's an imaginative things happening in this office
不必那么多条条框框
Alright  we're not just working in a box
我们用两百万
We got the two million
把卡迈因和酋长聚到了一起
to put Carmine and the Sheikh together
混蛋
Punk
我喜欢这种工作方式
I like being on the side of the line
但是某人被冷落了
But  someone had been left out
我们成功是因为小心谨慎
We succeed because
we stayed small
我帮你钓到艾尔威了
I got you Carl Elwey
他买卖赃画 做假银行单
He bought stolen art,sold fake bank CD's.
这就算一个了
That's enough,that's one.
我再帮你抓三个人 不包括政客
I got you three one  no politicians
你不干不行
You're gonna do this  because
因为你没有选择 你在为我工作
you got no choice
You work for me
你一直在改变规则
Now  you keep changing the rules
被权力冲昏头脑
Now  you're getting a   little
power drunk
你想弄醒他吗 伊迪丝
now you wanna tell him,Edith?
You wanna wake him up?
当然不行
Oh  no  I said  we shouldn't do any of it
欧文 你知道我的意思
Irving  you know I said that
我支持里奇
So  now I support Richie
他有目标
要么不干 要干就干大的
He's got vision
Do it heavy  or don't do it
就他这种人把美国毁掉了
不是我
I mean  he's the one ruining America
not me
我他妈怎么把美国毁了的
How the fuck am I ruining America?
因为人们刚从水门事件和越战中恢复过来
Because  people just got over
Wategate and Vietnam  alright?
你就要往政客身上泼脏水
You're gonna shit all over
politicians again?
就因为你想干大事 被提拔
Is it because you wanna be a big shot
and get a promotion?
不 我是从大处着想
No  I'm thinking big
这将令人难以置信
Alright  this is gonna be fantastic
接下来要视频监控
We're doing video surveillance
我要竭尽全力做这件事
I'm doing this
from the feet up!
你办不来的
You will never do it properly
你用的是政府那的一套
Because you got too much government attitude
不够低调和滑头
to be small and sleek
我像越共一样狡猾
I'm like the fucking Vietcong,alright?
我神出鬼没 神不知鬼不觉
I'm in and i'm out
I was there the whole time
任何人都发现不了
You don't know it  alright?
这他妈的是伪装的艺术
That's the fucking art of becoming somebody
获取别人的信任
who people can pin their beliefs
和梦想
and their dreams on
这种事你做不到
You can't do it
喜来登大酒店订间套房如何
How about the suite at the Sheraton Hotel?
和卡迈因·鲍里托谈重建大西洋城的事?
For Carmine Polito and rebuilding Atlantic City?
需要给酋长订个豪华房间
We need a luxury for the Sheikh
得了吧 卡迈因以前经常干这些勾当
Oh  Come on! Carmine does backdoor dealings all the time
这不是在讨价还价 欧文
We don't have a budget for that  Irving
你要拉下马的是
We are gonna knock
一个市长 众议院代表
The Mayor
the speaker of the state assembly
你要把他彻底拉下马 对吗
You gotta knock him off
his fucking feet  Alright?
你必须要让他感到受宠若惊
He's gotta feel like he is out of his league
提供这样一笔交易
What you're offering this deal
I mean  this is unheard of
在新泽西州 甚至这个国家都闻所未闻
In the state of New Jersey
Maybe  in the whole fucking country alright?
酋长要贷两百万给我们
Hey Sheikh  you're loaning us million
of dollars
重建大西洋城
to rebuild Atlantic City
你他妈开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
这么大一笔钱
That's gigantic alright
市长想要见现金
The mayor  he's gonna want to see the cash
要看到确切的账户
He's gonna want to see an account
立马就要见到
He's gonna want to see it right now
他要核实
And  he will check
这就是进行不下去的原因
That's why  this meeting isn't happening
因为 首先
Because to get millions
你得有两百万
you need millions
我们已经弄到了
We already did it
啥
What?
我们从局里拨了两百万 放帐上三天
We got the Bureau to park
two million dollars for three days
账户也有了
We got the account numbers
你和他
WE  meaning you and him?
对 我和那家伙
Yeah  me and that guy
她告诉我的
She showed me
告诉他 我们的事情
Show him  our thing?
你瞒着我
You did that without me?
开玩笑
Are you kidding?
你想怎样
What are you gonna do?
你在耍我
You're playing me?
还是在耍他
Or you're doing this
you're playing him
你要是耍花招 后果很严重
very bad for you if playing me
你得做出决定了 小子
You're gonna have to decide
for yourself  kid
我对你已经毫无保留
I just laid everything
on the table
真让人激动
This is all very exciting
我没想过会这样
I didn't know I could be like this
疯狂
To be wild
拉一个坏人下马
You know we're taking down
bad guys
政界的大人物
A very important politician
我是里奇·迪马索探员
This is agent  Richie Dimaso
我把7.5万美金放入手提箱
I'm placing 75 thousand dollars
in this briefcase
将交给市长卡迈因·鲍里托
for Mayor Carmine Polito
To procure
用来获得大西洋城的赌场执照和建筑许可
Casino lisence and building permits
for Atlantic City
我不明白这是怎么回事
太奇怪了
I don't know what that is
This is very weird
莫名其妙
到底怎么回事
This is very weird
I don't know what the fuck that is
市长先生
Mr Mayor?!
请留步 听我解释
Please  stop listen
如果那些蠢货冒犯了您 我向您道歉
I apoligize  if that punk offended you
非常抱歉
- 没什么 谢谢
I really apologize
- I'm alright  Thank you
跟他们一起弄的我很尴尬
No  i'm fucking embarassed
to be associated with that guy at all
我能跟您说两句吗
Can i just say  something to you please
不要错失良机好吗
Don't loose this opportunity
to fucking Florida  Alright?
就因为那个
Just because of some
白痴顾问说了些废话
Bullshit
from that punk advisor
With his diploma  alright
他连学历都没有
Who could never get into
the school that we come from
别失去这个机会
Don't loose that opportunity
你从哪来
- 布朗克斯
Where are you from?
- From the Bronx
大广场区 164号大街
Grand Concourse
164th street
我有许多朋友住在那里
I got lot of friends
who lives up there
托马索餐厅
Yeah  got Tomasso's
你知道亚瑟大道的托马索吗
Tomasso's on Arthur avenue?
是的 他们家的蛤蜊
Yeah  the clams there
蛤蜊 对 他妈的太好吃了
Clams  oh  those are fucking to die
for  those things
我在那边待过一阵子
喜欢那里
I haven't been there in a while
I like that place
嗯 听我说
Well  you know what
我能叫你卡迈因吗
Can I call you Carmine?
卡迈因
You know  Carmine
我心脏都快跳出来了
Hey  my fucking heart is done
从楼上跑下来 我不经常跑步
Running down
i'm not used to running
那边的那个酒店
It's a lot of green grass
有很多绿化的地方 楼上 好吗
in that hotel room  Up there
Alright?
所有的交易细节都要经过你
And  all the deals
will flow through you
双方都会严肃对待
You'll get a serious piece
on both ends  alright?
你的要求都能实现
You do with that
what you will  man
我又不是假的
我有妻儿的
I live in the real world  Alright?
I'm a family man
还要养家糊口
I got mouths to feed and
everything like that
我们必须
But  you know   this
直截了当地运作这件事
You gotta grease it directly
不要中间人 不废话
用阿拉伯的方式
No middle man  no bullshit
It's the Arab's way
就这样
That's it  that's it
嗯 我明白
Alrigh  look I understand
这是千载难逢的好机会
It's a great opportunity
you understand
今天的见面让我情绪受到些影响
I was a little thrown by
going into meeting with somebody
事情有点突如其来
I didn't even know would be in there
我也一样
- 我会直接和你们交易
I was thrown as well
- Understand  I'll deal with you directly
没有中间人和什么乱七八糟的
Not any middle man or
any other bullshit
可以
- 直接交易
Done!
- I'll deal with you directly
我喜欢你 看法一致
I like you
Eye to eye
我可以和你做生意
- 不错
We can do business together
- That's fine
你认识这人多久了
How long have you known this guy?
以前和他共事过吗
You've work with this guy  before?
我必须和他共事 他是酋长手下的人
I gotta work with him  It's the Sheikh
我还是要见酋长本人
But  I still need to meet the Sheikh
没问题
Okay?
- Done  After you
我要去卡姆登赴宴
I'm going out for dinnner
跟卡迈因和太太们
with Carmine and the wives in Camden
谁
Who?
卡迈因和我们双方的太太
Carmine and myself with the wives
什么 不带我
What? Without me?!
他讨厌你
我又能怎样
He doesn't like you
What do you want from me?
我叫他回来拿钱
I got him to come back
take the money
你在后面录监控
You got him on tape
我又不能强迫他喜欢你
I can't make him like you
我做了我该做的
I did my job
你有没有告诉他 我和你共事
Did you tell him you're working with me
我是酋长的顾问
And  that i'm the Sheikh's associate
我他妈的说过了
他不喜欢你
I just fucking told you!
He doesn't like you
让他跟一个正常人出去吧
该死的
I mean  let him have a nigh out with a human being
For fucks sake
他很快就蹲大牢了
Alright? He is going to jail soon
You're done with him
你录下他受贿的证据
You got him on tape taking a bribe
卡迈因必须跟我交易
Carmine has got to deal with me  Irving
我们要利用卡迈因
不不不
We're gonna use Carmine
Yeah  no  no  no
利用卡迈因逮到更多人
Carmine will get us other people
什么 谁
What? Like who?
卡迈因要拿酋长的钱付给别人
Carmine is gonna use the Sheikh's
to pay off people
你他妈疯了吗
Are you fucking nuts?
Are you
让卡迈因给酋长展示大西洋城
We're gonna let Carmine
show the Sheikh Atlantic City
他的重修计划
看看谁会出现
How he's gonna renovate hotels
and see who shows up!
不管钱付给谁 执照 开赌场
Whoever the Sheikh pays off
For lisences and casinos
那些人就是我们要抓的
That's who  we're gonna go after
我们要把他们一网打尽
We are gonna go after all of them!
这就是你所谓的不抓政客
- 对
No more politicians?
- Yeah
你知道这他妈有多危险吗
You realize how fucking dangerous that is?
你这人简直他妈的不讲理
There's no fucking
reasoning with you
伊迪丝和我一直顺风顺水
Edith and I
were so sucessful for so long
就是因为小心谨慎
Because  we kept it just
small enough
你现在把我们置身这么危险的境地
You're taking us to a very
fucking dangerous place
这么大的数目
with very serious numbers!
你那么成功
If you're that sucessful
怎么还落到我手里了
how come you wound up with me right now?
听我发号施令
Taking orders from me
你要带你老婆去赴宴
You're taking your wife out to dinner?
你那该死的老婆  我没听错吧
Your fucking wife,did i hear you correctly?
你就光听见这个了
That's the one thing you heard me say?
我只是觉得很震惊
I just find it rather shocking  that's all
我要在宴席中应付两个太太
I get to handle two wives
with one dinner Alright?
我带罗莎琳去 让她把嘴闭紧
I take Rosalyn out
she keeps her mouth shut
让她看到我的工作合法
She sees that my work is legitimate
我得让我的孩子
I get to keep my kid and
I get to keep
和“那该死的老婆”开心
that fucking wife happy
两边的老婆都开心
Both wives happy
理查德 你在干吗
Richard  what are you doing?
理查德
别在卫生间里吃饭
Richard don't eat in the bathroom
我说过多少次了
I told you so many times!
戴安娜带了拿破仑酒
And Diane brought napoleons
快出来祷告
Come out of the bathroom and pray
老天 你干了什么
Oh  my god! What did you do?
鱼缸里的过滤器坏了
The filter is broken in the fishtank
出毛病了
It's the problem
妈 过滤器是你负责的 我负责放碎石子
Your job is to do the filter,mine's to do the gravel
过滤器要是坏了
When you don't do the filter right
鱼都活不成了
You get all the fish die
知道吗
- 我搞不定上面的那玩意
See?
- I can't that top of the thing
请保佑理查德
And  please help Richard
让他和戴安娜结婚 我就能抱孙子了
to marry Diane so that
i may have granchildren
祝愿教皇有更多的追随者
And  the Pope may have more followers
感谢赐予我们食物
And  please bless this food
That we are about to eat
理查德
- 你好
Richard?
- Yea  hello?
你好
- 哪位
Hi
- Who's this?
伊迪丝
It's Edith
坐下给我好好祈祷
Sit down and pray properly
你还好吧
Are you alright?
我很好 只是有点
Yeah  yeah I'm fine
It's just
孤单 欧文和卡迈因去吃饭了
i'm alone  you know?
Irving is out with
噢 是啊
Carmine
Oh  yes that's right
他和卡迈因吃饭 还带着他妻子
He went out with Carmine
and his wife
你心里一定不太好受
Yeah  you must not feel
so good about that
理查德 坐下
Richar sit down
等等 是谁
你和谁在一起
Wait  who is there?
Who are you with?
没 就是别人
Oh  no  It's just people
别人 我是你未婚妻 理查德
People? I'm your fiance  Richard?
我都不知道你已经订婚了
Oh  you got a fiance
You are engaged
我不知道 我没未婚妻
I don't know  I don't
have a fiance
你不知道
You don't know?
你有没有未婚妻都不知道
You don't know
if you have a fiance
我不…知道
I don't know
鱼缸的过滤器坏了
The fish filter is broken
嗯 有意思
Hmm  interesting
你想和我一起吗
You wanna get together?
理查德 快点把鱼缸修好
Richard  Do something about the fishtank!
54号街?
54th street?
好 54号街
Okay  54th street
好的
Okay  great
刚才那通电话是这样的
That's what the phone call is about
人家都以为
Everybody thought
"里奇只会坐在办公室里
"Oh  Richie DiMaso is
gonna stay in the office
摆弄摆弄文件"
pushing papers "
事实不是 妈
That's not gonna happen  Mom
我在场外指挥
I'm outside on the field
让别人为我工作
I got peoples working for me
我的点子 我导演了整个计划
My ideas  I'm running the show
我就是组织进攻的四分卫
I'm the quaterback
我不会跟任何人妥协 妈
I'm not gonna settle for no one  Mom
你好吗 罗科
Rocco  how are you?
罗科 鸡肉切得薄一点好吗
Rocco we like the
chicken very thin alright
用红酱汁
Look the way you dresses the chicken
点缀的鸡肉
With the red sauce
真的很不错
They're so good
就是这
Here it is! This is it
这里这里 看到没
This right here  this right here
Look at this
太棒了
This is so  good  So good
非常美味
This is so nice
谢谢你 罗科
Thank you  Rocco
- Thank you  Rocco
我相信 你如何待人
I believe that  you should treat people;
别人就如何待你
The way that  you want to be treated
这话是耶稣说的吗
Did Jesus say that  or something?
可能说过
He may have
帮助别人比获得金钱更重要
Always take a favour over money
耶稣也说过这句
I think  Jesus said that as well
我不敢肯定说没说过这句
I don't know if he said the second one
但前一句好像说过
He might have said the first one
我经常把家具挪来挪去
I chipped this moving furniture
最近对这个上瘾
It's my new obsession
挪家具 重新装饰
会让我感觉好一些
Moving  redecorating
makes me feel better
让自己忙碌
like  exercise  But  there is this
这款指甲油只有瑞士能买到
There is this top coat
That you can only get from Switzerland
没了它我都不知道该怎么办
And  I don't know what i'm gonna do
快用完了
B'cos  i'm running out of it
我爱死这个味道了
- 回来送你一点
But  i love the smell of it
- Oh  I can get it for you
太棒了
- 当然
That would be amazing
- Of course!
这款指甲油闻起来
There is something   the top coat
有点像香水
It's like  perfumy
但貌似还有点腐烂的味道
But  there is also something rotten?
我知道听起来很奇怪
And  i know that sounds crazy
但让人欲罢不能
闻一下 是不是
But  I can't get enough of it
Smell it  it's true
多莉  没错吧
Dolly  historically
世界上最好的香水
the best perfumes in the world
都加了些肮脏的东西
They're all laced with something nasty
真的诶
It is true!
欧文很喜欢
Irving loves them
他都闻不够
He can't get enough of that smell
意犹未尽
I can't get enough
卡迈因 闻一闻
Carmine  smell the nails
又香又臭
Sweet and sour
腐烂又美味
Rotten and delicious
闻起来像鲜花
It smells like flowers
和垃圾在一起的鲜花
Flowers  but with garbage
给我的感觉有点像香菜味
You know what that is for me
It's coriander for me
把他魂都钩没了
That's what hooks him
他经常回来找这个味道
He always comes back for it
他马上就会说
He's gonna say
“我们来谈生意吧”
'We have to talk business'
五 四 三 二 一
four  three  two   One
多莉 我和卡迈因能谈谈生意吗
Dolly  Can me and Carmine talk about business here?
不用不用 我没醉
I'm not this drunk
你未婚妻难道不想出来吗
Didn't your fiance
want to come out tonight?
不
Yeah  uh
我不知道
I don't know  Yeah
No
噢 天 对不起
Oh  God  i'm sorry
对不起
不必谈这个
I'm sorry
We don't have to talk about it
我开玩笑的- 没关系
I was just teasing you
- That's alright
你是不是在想 我怎么是这个结果
Ever think like  ' How did I end up here?'
我的生活为何那么糟糕
Like  how my life become
screwed? Ever think of that?
你在想
And  you wonder like
我就不能换个好地方吗
是不是
Can I ever gonna get up to a better place
Or  this is it
有这种感觉吗
- 是
You feel like that?
- Yeah
想过
Yeah  I do
我理解你的处境
I definitely  know that
抱歉 我们不一定非要跳舞
I'm sorry  we don't have to go dancing
可以喝咖啡 聊聊
We can go have coffee or talk
不
- No  no  no
不 我需要
No  no  I need this
我想和你跳舞
Please  I need to go
dancing with you
拜托了
Please
宝贝 我们去跳舞
Okay baby
Let's go dancing
快点出来
Hurry up and get out of this
我真他妈的喜欢你
I really fucking like you
我也是
Yeah  yeah
I like you too
我想真正活一次
I wanna live
Like  for real
认真爱一回
No more fake shit
Right?
等我们都坦诚相待时
We're gonna wait until we
decide  we fall for real
那时再上床
That's when we fuck
Not till then
好吗
Okay?
好
Okay
不再弄虚作假
No more fake shit
我操 老娘要上厕所
Fuck me I got to pee
出去
Get out
大伙们
Boys
那边那个家伙
This guy right here  Julius?
欧文·罗森菲尔德
This guy Irving Rosenfeld
你们知道他要干吗嘛
You know what he's gonna do?
他要把酋长带到大西洋城
He is gonna bring the Sheikh to Atlantic City
我们就能够建度假村
Where we can build all those resorts there
让每个人都有工作
Put everybody back to work
他将让这个社区
He's gonna get this community;
这个州
He's gonna get this state
重新振作起来 回到应有的面貌
Back on it's feet
To where it belongs
是不是
Isn't that right?
他会让税基增长
He's gonna grow our tax base
增加成千上万的工作岗位
and creat thousands of jobs
为所有人
for everyone!
明白吗
Do you understand that?
大家明白我的意思吗
You know what that means?
敬欧文!
To Irving!
这家伙很伟大
Come on  this guy right here
He's got a big heart
万一实现不了呢
Let's just say  that
it didn't work out?
什么意思
What do you mean?
当然会实现
像你我这样的人
Of course  it's gonna work out
Guys like you and me
我们梦想 我们努力
right? We dream and we build
决不放弃
We never give up
决不退缩
We never quit
我能问个事儿吗
Hey  can i ask you a question?
当然
Yeah  sure
酋长是黑人吗
Is the Sheikh black?
酋长他是阿拉伯人
The Sheikh  he is uh
He is an Arab
那就属于黑人了
That's black isn't it
我知道问得很蠢
I know it's just
a dumb question but
我就想知道
I was wondering
为什么这样问
Why are you asking?
我想安排酋长
I would like to
arrange
the Sheikh
去看看卡姆登 看看卡姆登的人民
to see Camden.To see the people of Camden
我服务的人民 热爱的人民
People I serve,people I love
黑人和波多黎各人居多
almost black and Puerto Rican
欧文  我真的想让他看见
Irv  i really want him to see
他的举动给社会带来多大帮助
How good this is going to be
for the community
我们准备好迎接这个机遇了
How ready we are for
this opportunity
也能让他知道钱都花向何处
And  he could see how far
his dollar would go
你看呢
You know what i mean
What do you think?
可以的
Yeah  we can do that  yeah
真好
Ah  good
哦对了 我有东西想给你
Oh  hey  I got something
I wanna give you
送你个礼物
Come on
I got you a gift
出去说 快被那些主妇们吵死了
Let's get out of here
The wive's gonna kill us
就是这
Here you go
这是什么
What is it?
微波炉
It's a Microwave
什么都能加热
It heats up everything
意面 千层面 肉丸
Pasta  Lasagna  meatballs
什么都行
- 真的吗
Whatever
- Really?
新鲜玩意 用来加热食物
It's science  Yeah
it's that how it heats up the food
科学发明
It's scientific
你特意买来送给我
And  you specifically  bought this science oven for me?
对啊
Yeah
交个新朋友
A new friend
谢谢你
Thank you
记住别放金属
Don't put metal it
来 咱们走吧
Come on  let's get out of here
我需要一架飞机 在泰特波罗机场
I need a Jet at Teterboro
给酋长准备架飞机
I need a Jet at Teterboro for the Sheikh
不需要飞机
You don't need a Jet
让他自己在肯尼迪机场走一走
Let him walk to the curb at JFK
这样不行
That's not how it works
必须装得彻底
You gotta start from the feet up
什么意思
That doesn't mean anything
What does that mean?
意思是要坚定立场
It means you gotta be committed
做事要全力以赴
Means  you gotta be committed
to something in your life
老天 可以吗
For Christ sake  alright?
我要在泰特波罗机场给酋长准备一架飞机
I want a Jet at Teterboro
for the Sheikh
小飞机就行
装装样子
It can be a small jet
Doesn't even have to take off
我知道你担心花局里的钱
I know you're so worried about
the money the bureau's gonna fucking spend
就在跑道上起飞着陆一下 行吗
It can take off and land
on the tarmac  okay?!
好吧 批准你用一小时飞机
Alright  you can have the jet
for an hour
只能在泰特波罗机场起飞降落
- 给我飞机了
But takes off and lands at Teterboro
- I got the jet?
是的
- 谢谢
You got the jet
- Alright  thank you
等一下 跟我讲完冰钓的故事
Wait  tell me the rest of
the ice fishing story
说到哪儿了
Where was I?
你爸冒着大暴雪去了湖边 快讲
Your father walks in the blizzard
at the lake  come on  C'mon!
我和哥哥提前去钓鱼
Okay  when my brother and I
were on the ice
我看到我父亲向我们走来
and my father came out of the house;
and I could see him coming
手里提着灯笼 当时下着暴雪
Holding the lantern and there's blizzard
我知道他一定很生气
and I knew he was gonna be angry
我跑去拦住他
So  i went to intercept my father
因为要是他看见我哥在钓鱼
B'cos I knew if he saw
what my brother was doing
我哥就遭殃了
- 噢 你试图保护你哥
He was gonna kill him
- Oh  you tried to protect your brother
但没保护成
你感到难过
But  you couldn't
And that's why you feel bad  b'cos
因为你担心我 想保护我
you're trying to protect me
and you're worried about me
就是这个故事吧
讲的是保护
Is that what the story is about?
It's about protection
不 不是保护
- 哈  - 不是
No  it's not about protection
- No?  - No
算了
Alright  fine
“别把金属放到微波炉里 罗莎琳”
Don't put metal in that science oven
Roselyn
他老是把我当小孩子
He always treats me like a fucking child.
我想干什么你管得着吗
Do whatever I want
又着火啦
Another fire!
别 丹尼! 别用那个 是空的
No Danny! Not that one,that one's empty
用那个大的
We gotta get the big one
我告诉过你别放金属
I told you not to put metal
in the science oven
你这是干吗
- 别大惊小怪的
What did you do that for?
- Don't make such a big deal
买个新的就是了
Just get another one
我就想要卡迈因给我的
I don't want another one
I want the one Carmine gave me
哦 卡迈因 我就想要卡迈因给我的
Oh  Carmine  I want the one Carmine
gave me
卡迈因 卡迈因 你娶他得了
Carmine  carmine Why don't you just marry Carmine
再送你个小金微波炉串起来挂脖上
Get a little gold microwave
and put it on chain around your neck
你想像卡迈因一样
You wanna be more like Carmine?
怎么不学学人家 干一番事业出来
Why don't you build something
like he does
而不是开你的皮包公司
Instead of your empty deals
跟你这该死的微波炉一样
They're just like your fucking science oven
我听说这玩意把所有营养都破坏了
You know  I read that
it takes all of nutritions out of our food
什么都没有 跟你的生意一样 屁都没有
It's empty  just like your deals
Empty  empty!
胡扯
- 我可没胡扯
That's bullshit
- It's not bullshit
我读过篇文章 看
I read it in an article
Look
普尔弗·德尔写的
By Pulver Deur
弄这玩意回来
Bringing something into this house
营养都破坏了
That's gonna take all nutritions out
of our food
还差点把房子烧了
and light our house on fire?
你该感谢上帝 让你遇到我
Thank God for me
你能做到的
Alright you got this
你今晚不能去卡迈因的派对
I don't think
you should come to Carmine's party  tonight
顺便说一下 你真美
You look beautiful
By the way
别看着我
Don't look at me
行吗
Alright?
别看我的腿 我的头
Don't look at my legs
don't look at my head
别闻我的头发
Don't smell my hair
别问我是谁
Don't ask me how I am
别跟我谈规则之外的事 因为我们结束了
Don't talk to me outside
of this rules cos  i'm done
站到伞里来
Just stand still
Get in the umbrella  Come on
卡迈因想要罗莎琳去
Just  Carmine wants
Rosalyn
我不在乎
to come
- I don't care!
听好了 我不在乎谁去
You aren't listening
I don't care if Rosalyn comes
做好你的事就行了
Just do your job  okay?
你曾经是我的一切 现在你什么都不是
You're nothing to me
Until you're everything
我不是罗莎琳 我忍受不了这些屁话
I'm not Rosalyn
I'm not gonna put up with that shit
这飞机真他妈不错
That's a fucking jet  right?
很好
- 这是行动的一部分
It's good
- It's the kinda moves you need to make
帕考·赫尔南德斯
我是里奇·迪马索
Paco Hernandez?
I'm Richie DiMasso
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you in person
这位是欧文·罗森菲尔德
This is Irving Rosenfeld
我是帕考·赫尔南德斯  高兴见到你
Paco Hernandez  nice to meet you
帕考  等等 他不是阿拉伯人
Paco  wait no  no He's not an Arab
不 墨西哥人
No  Mexican  from Tucson
我的人呢
艾尔呢?
Where is my guy?
Where's Al?
我皇后区的朋友哪去了
My friend from Queens
Where is he?
你搞什么
- 他是FBI的人
What are you doing?
- I gotta hire an FBI guy
会说阿拉伯语吗
You speak any Arabic?
会  As-salamu alaykum
Yeah  As-salamu alaykum
就这
- 我会说好几个短语
That's it?
- No  i have a couple of phrases
这就是你所谓的全力以赴 混蛋
From feet up  you motherfucker
What are you doing? C'mon
尽量表现正常一点
Act normal  that's it
Just seem all like
记住你不会说英语 千万别说漏
You can't barely understand english
You can't speak it
能少说话就少说 看我眼色行事
You say as little as possible
you follow my lead
明白
Alright?
谁是负责人
我还以为是你
Who's running this?
I thought you're running this
是我负责
但我们得听他的建议
I am running this
We gotta listen to him
这家伙很有眼光
He's the guy with the vision
我有眼光
你知道我有眼光
I got the vision?
You know the vision I had?
你刚刚当着我的面
You just kissed my girl
Right outside
亲了我的女人
- 我还以为你们分手了
That's what vision I have
- I thought you guys broke up
我那是赞美你
I'm giving you a compliment
怎么了
What's going on?
别担心
Don't worry about it  alright?
这把刀送给市长
I got a knife
This is for the mayor
这是你给市长的礼物
看着我
You gotta present it  to the mayor
Just look at me
看着我的眼睛
Alright  look me in the eye
这对你很重要
这把刀 一定要演好
This means a lot to you
Right? That knife  play it
双手呈上
You present it  alright?
一生的友谊 明白吗
要发自肺腑的
Friendship for life  alright
You gotta feel it
非常神圣  能做到吗
- 神圣
Sacred  Can you do it?
- Sacred
要有说服力
- 首先你自己要相信它很神圣
Sell it
- If you believe it  sacred
这是圣物
- 这些细节
They are sacred  alright?
- listen  the details  That's what makes
造就了这个天才
- 又来你又恭维我
This guy a genius
- Again? You're complimenting me again
伤口上撒盐
Rubbing salt in the wound?
你干什么
- 我这是赞美
What are you?
- I'm complimenting you
还有疑问吗
You got any other questions?
我觉得这次的行动代号很无礼
Yeah  i think the name
of the operation is offensive
ABSCAM 阿拉伯骗局 种族歧视啊
ABSCAM
Arab Scam? It's racist
开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
你一个墨西哥人 管这么多干吗
What do you care?
You're a Mexican
你好 酋长 我的朋友
Hello  Sheikh
欢迎
Welcome!
我代表新泽西州
On behalf of the
great state of New Jersey
欢迎您的来访
I wanna welcome you to New Jersey
不好意思 我太紧张了
I'm sorry,I'm very nerves
谢谢 谢谢你
Thank you  thank you
今晚准备了一场盛大的派对
We have a great party planned
for this evening
你说什么
不让我去
What are you talking about
I can't go?
我刚做了头发化了妆
I just did my hair
and make up and everything!
酋长是个特别的人物
The Sheikh's a very particular
这是国际文化礼节
It's an international
cultural protocol  You know
国际礼节
什么破玩意
International Protocol
What the fuck are you talking about?
别接 千万别
Do not answer that
Do not answer!
你好
- 罗伯特·斯潘塞找欧文
Hello?
- Robert Spencer for Irving
我不认识罗伯特·斯潘塞
Robert Spencer
I don't know a Robert Spencer
有何贵干
- 我是他的生意伙伴
What do you want?
- I'm a business associate
他是谁
Who is that?
老天
我说过别打来
For god's sake
I told you not to call here
增加两名联邦探员
Two more Federal agents tonight
什么
No  what?
两名FBI
- 不
Two Feds
- No
给酋长当保镖
I need them
bodyguards for the Sheikh
不 人手太多 会失控的
No  no  Too many guys
too many to control  No
欧文 记住谁是老大
Irving? Remember who's
in charge here
罗莎琳 挂掉分机
Rosalyn  get off the extention
我没接
I'm not on it
听着 别再往我家打了
Look  don't call here again  alright
Don't call at home
好的
Alright
这是生意电话
别打岔行吗
It's a business call
Don't interrupt  Alright?
联邦探员
FBI
Federal Agents?
重要人物的保镖 就这样
It's bodyguards for visiting dignitaries.That's all
干什么 国税局查税
What is it? An IRS thing
Like a tax investigation?
乱说什么
Why you gotta say that?
这就是为什么不带你去 这事很复杂
That's why I can't invite you.
你惹上麻烦了吗
Are you in trouble?
别多管闲事
Stop being nosy
我是多管闲事 因为你什么都瞒着我
Well,I'm nosy,cos  you never tell me anything
能清理下冰箱吗 别总给我添麻烦
Can you clean up this fridge? What're you causing trouble for all the time
别接
- 你好
Do not answer that!
- Hello?
我是卡迈因
It's Carmine
嗨 卡迈因 我们正说到你呢
Oh  hi  Carmine
We're just talking about you
欧文真讨厌
Yeah  Irving is being a mean  boring man
不让我去你们的派对
Saying that he doesn't want me tonight
跟他说这样做不对
Tell him he is crazy!
我同意
你来跟他说
Well  I agree
Tell him yourself
你不来还能叫派对吗
It wouldn't be a party without you
你能想到吗
Can you imagin?
你一定要来
Cos  you're coming
好 你跟他说
Yeah  Tell him yourself
欧文  你这样可不好
你太太一定要来
Irving  you're crazy
Your wife is coming
别开玩笑
她是派对的灵魂人物
You're kidding me
She's the life of the party
我们邀请她了
We enlist her
我可是灵魂人物
I'm the life of the party
你知道她这人有点反复无常
You know what she's like
she is unpredictable
别说老娘坏话 卡迈因怎么说
Hey  don't talk about me  like that!
What is Carmine saying?
卡迈因喜欢我
Carmine loves me
今晚真的很重要
This is really big night for us
You understand?
你必须带太太来
C'mon  you gotta bring your wife
多莉还给她准备了特别礼物
Dolly has got something special for her  right?
来听听
Listen  listen
我给你准备了指甲油 甜心
I got the nail polish for you  sweetie
怎么了
What is it?
告诉我
Tell me
你要带小情人来
What is it?
You got a girlfriend coming?
拜托 我们是朋友
C'mon  i thought we are friends
像男人一样面对
明白吗 带你太太来
Look  we're handling this like men
You understand? Bring your wife
我们会玩得很愉快
We'll have a good time
派对上见
We'll see you there
It'll be fun
这是市长的命令 再见
That's an order from your mayor
Goodbye
你开心了
去准备吧
Alright  you happy?
Go get ready
是的 我很开心
Yes  I am happy
我知道你是谁
I know who you are
我知道这狐狸精是谁 欧文
I know who that is  Irving
真漂亮
- 这就是大厅
Oh  it looks beautiful
- So  this is the lobby
一周前就提醒过你们 这地方很糟
Reminds you a week ago
this place was a mess
最有价值的是这幅壁画
But  what existed was this
plaster work
瞧瞧这细节 太美了
Look at the detail
It's beautiful
我儿子画的
来告诉他你画的什么
My son is a craftman
Please  tell him what you did
我画了鸟 天空 树木 错视画
I did birds,sky,wood,
Trompe l'oeil
这些都是我们修缮的
We restore all of this,you see?
省了五千万
看着我
This saved us 50 million
Look at me
立马省了五千万
50 million
right of the bat
像这样
Like that
我放弃一笔贷款
I waived a loan
Got the help  right?
而不是从头建造新建筑
Instead of constructions having to
build ground up new
我们不建新的
We don't do 'new'
而是修整翻新
We renovate  right
我们利用临时资金
We used some temporary funds
弄了这些赌桌 轮盘赌
给人们享乐
The gaming tables  some roulette
for people to have a good time
公益事业
It's for charity
男孩女孩俱乐部和文艺项目
for the Boys and Girls Club and
some art programs
这是海景房
This is the ocean room
吧台旁边的那几位先生 看见了吗
There's some gentlemen
sitting over there at the bar
他们加一起都有130岁了
That's a 130 years sitting right there
That's how many times between them
全美国最大的赌场就在他们手里
They run the biggest casinos
in the united states
我们要跟他们合作
- 是的
We have to work with them
- Right
好消息是
The good new is
他们知道如何运作
they know how it's done
They get it done
这点你不必担心
人人都为他们挣钱
You don't have to worry
Everyone makes their money
你意思是他们是黑手党
- 对 同时也是生意人
You mean the mob?
- Yes  but they're business men
花不花时间在他们身上由你决定
Spend at much or little time
with them as you like
但是我们必须和他们做交易
But  we do have to deal with them
去和他们打个招呼吧
All we gotta do is go and say  'Hello'
Just gotta say  Hi
和他们谈话之前先确认一下
We gotta confirm before
we talk to those guys
有什么好确认的
Confirm?
What is there to confirm about
赌场大佬
The casino guys
他们是赌场大佬
they're casino guys!
欧文 我们大老远跑来不就为这个
Irving  we came all this way
We should be here
你们都怕什么
What is everybody scared of
你们都怕那几个家伙
Those are the guys
that you guys are all scared of?
就那几个
我可不怕
Those guys over there?
They don't scare me
罗莎琳  罗莎琳?
Rosalyn  Rosalyn?
欧文  事情不是这样搞的
Irving  that's not the way to do this
我喜欢
I love this!
知道吗 那几个人怕你们
They are scared of you guys,you know that
去给我拿点汽水和披萨来
Kids  I want you to go up and
get some soda and pizzas please
这下惨了
That's disaster
这屋子装修的很差劲
I think they got this room  all wrong
换你会怎么装
Yeah? What would you do?
全部用黑色和金色
I would do in all black and gold
吧台像一面金光闪闪的大镜子
I would do this bar like a big
warm  golden mirror
听起来不错
- 谢谢
Sounds beautiful
- Oh  thank you
我很期待是因为她长得漂亮
I expect cos she's so beautiful
头发也漂亮
and I love her hair
不好意思 她是你妻子吗
I'm sorry  Is she your wife?
她是我妻子
she is my wife.
瞧瞧这几位先生
Look at these fine gentlemen
你好吗
- 很高兴见到你
How are you?
- Good to see you
够了
That's enough of that right now.
他是个扫兴鬼 好无聊
Oh  i know because he's a party pooper
He's so boring
允许我介绍一下阿布杜拉酋长
May I present  Sheikh Abdullah
来阿布达比
Gentlemen  from Abu Dhabi
酋长先生 这些人很专业
Sheikh  these are professionals
他们经营全美最棒的赌场
They run the best casinos in United States
酋长先生
Mr Sheikh
郑重告诉您
As a sign of our seriousness
特莱吉奥先生从迈阿密赶来见您
Mr Tallegio came from Miami to meet you tonight
特莱吉奥先生
Mr Tallegio?
为什么没提前通知特莱吉奥先生要来
Why didn't you tell me  Mr Tallegio is here
他在里面
He's in the back room
这是不尊重的表现
It's a sign of disrespect to talk
第一次谈生意
- 不是的
business  On the first meeting
- That's not true
我不知道你在说什么 他搞错了
Yeah  I don't know what you're talking about
He's got it all wrong
你要让人家在里面一直等着
You wanna leave him back there
in the back room waiting?
我们得去见他
We gotta meet him
我纽约来的朋友不知道这些习俗
My friend from New York
doesn't know the custom
欧文 我要找点乐子去
说不定会传染呢
Hey  Irving i'm gonna be having fun
Maybe  it will be contagious  huh?
你能相信吗 他对我那种态度
Can you believe
that he talk to me that way?
卡迈因
Carmine?
特莱吉奥先生来自迈阿密
Victor Tellegio was from Miami
他是梅耶·兰斯基的得力助手
He was Meyer Lansky's right hand man
作为一个打手他名声在外
With his prior reputation
as an enforcer from
20年前就无人不晓
杀人从不埋尸
20 years ago was known
to never bury a body;
把尸体直接扔大街上 杀鸡儆猴
B'cos  he felt it sent a stronger message
To leave it on the street
我们现在要跟这个家伙做生意
This is the guy
we now have to deal with
你确定不想出去转转 这是海景酒吧
Are you sure  you don't wanna
go out there  It's ocean bar
外面景色很好
- 我不出去
It's beautiful out there
- I don't have to go out there
我喜欢这里 旁边就是出口
I like it here
There is an exit
我像个幽灵
I'm like a ghost
没人知道我在这里
Nobody knows i am here
告诉他 我是来帮佛罗里达的朋友带话
Tell him  I speak
for our friends in Florida
非常高兴 这是我们一生的梦想
We're very excited
It's been our life long dream
在东海岸建一座赌城度假村
to build Casinos resorts
in the east coast
告诉他
You told him that
他们不想让犹太人赚钱
They don't want the Jews to make money
也不想让意大利人赚钱
They don't want the Italians to make money
更不想让黑人赚钱
They definitely don't want
the blacks to make money
之后的石油禁令
After  the oil embargo
汽油危机
gasoline crisis
慕尼黑惨案
The hijacking  the olympics
人们也不想看到阿拉伯人挣钱
They don't wanna see Arabs
make money
在我们的地盘上
Plus not on our soils
请你告诉他
I don't know  if you can tell him
in your own way
我做赌场四十年
I've been in the casino business
for forty years
这行比哪一行都要谨慎
It's scrutinised more careful
then any other business
卡迈因争取了赌博业合法化
Carmine made this legal  but
我们必须更加小心 以防政府收回
we must be careful or they
will take it away
特莱吉奥先生 你认为应该通过什么途径
So  Mr Tallegio  how do you think
we should approach this?
用什么办法
What do you wanna do?
要想拿到执照并保住它
If you wanna get the gaming
license and keep it
我们的投资者 酋长
We have to make our principle
investor here  The Sheikh
必须拥有美国国籍
An American citizen
快速办理国籍
Well,to expedite citizenship
要走特殊渠道
One that requires special treatment
哪些人能办这个
Well  you would know
the right people to do that
参议员 国会议员
U S Senators
U S congressmen Senators
太棒了
Wow! That's fantastic!
我看还是算了吧 风险太大了
I say  stay away from that
That's bad  That's trouble
拜托 欧文
Irving please?
这家伙哪来的
Who is this guy?
Who are you  huh?
你干什么的 农民
What are you  a farmer?
特莱吉奥先生 抱歉
他是欧文
Mr Tallegio  i'm sorry
this is  Irving
欧文·罗森菲尔德
He is Irving Rosenfeld
纽约商人
- 怎么回事 欧文
New York business man
- What's the matter  Irving?
有问题吗
- 没什么
What's the problem?
- Nothing  no problem
别瞎嚷嚷
Don't get your balls in an uproar
一切都很好
Everything is fine
Everything is good
都没问题
It's all good  It's all good
我只是希望
It's all good
I just hope
我们双方都没问题
the other part of this
is all good
都是货真价实的
And real
因为 我们就是货真价实的
Because  we are real
You know that
你和我们交易很可靠 有组织有背景
You deal with us
we are real organisation
可我都不知道对方什么来头
We're dealing with
we don't know what we're dealing with
他从哪来
Where is he from?
阿布达比
Abu Dhabi
阿联酋- 对
Oh  he's from the Emirates?
- Yeah
[阿拉伯语]我能信赖你吗
你得跟我说实话 听到了吗
有一说一
不扯淡
听到没有
要我重复吗
你在想什么
说啊
我觉得
I think  I think  what is
让他自己来说
Let him speak for himself
你们这些家伙在派对上也太严肃了
You guys are way too serious for a party
你们喝什么 喝酒了吗
What are you drinking? You got a drink?
你现在就跟我走
You got to come with me now
还等你演讲呢 - 我随后就到
the speech is waitting for you. - I'm right behind you.
相信我 随后就到
Trust me I'm right behind you
和你做生意很不错
我的投资很可靠
非常高兴认识你
这他妈有多巧
What are the fucking odds
碰上个迈阿密来的 会说阿拉伯语的意大利人
you got an italian guy from Miami
knowing Arabic
原来他在中东投资赌场
It turns out  he's got casino
investments  in the middle east
为了经营好生意 他花两年时间学阿拉伯语
And  he spent two years
learning it to keep the upper hand
听仔细了
Listen to me carefully
两周之内把一千万打到我们指定的账户
If you really put 10 million in
the bank of our choice
卡迈因 听好了
Carmine  listen me carefully
我要你两周内一千万到帐
You put 10 million in the bank or our choice
In the next two weeks  or
不然 不仅对酋长
Not only will the Sheikh feel something
也是对我们佛罗里达的朋友极大的不尊重
But  our friends in Florida
will feel deeply disrespected
当然还有我
So  will I
罗莎琳 跟我过来一下
Rosalyn  you need to come
with me  alright
你让我跟你一起
- 拜托 别这样
Oh  you want me to come with you?
- Please  just stop alright
我跟你走
Oh  you think I should
come with you?
把你的脏手拿开
Get your fucking hands off me
你个臭婊子
You fucking whore
她是我丈夫的婊子
This is my hausband's whore!
你留在这儿 亲爱的
You know,you stay here ritht now,darling.
你跟我来
You stay over here with me.
大家都冷静一下 我不知道怎么回事
Everybody just calm down.I don't know what's going on.
你没事吧
You alright?
放轻松
Take it easy
命中注定 随它去吧
Whatever is meant to be  will be
我也经常这么说
I always say that
是吗
- 是啊
You say that?
- Yeah
我们真是志趣相投呢
Kindred spirits
命中注定 随它去吧
Whatever is meant to be  will be
你到底在干什么
What the hell do you think
you are doing?
我干什么了
What do i think  what i'm doing?
你他妈的以为你在干什么
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
一边跑过来指责我跟人家调情
You're gonna come and just me
for flirting
一边在背后偷我老公那么多年
while you've been fucking
my hausband for how many years?!
你根本没搞清楚状况
You don't have a fucking clue
what's going on
看看我手上的戒指 我们都有孩子了
I got a ring on my finger
We have a child together!
他不爱你 罗莎琳 他爱的是我
He doesn't love you  Rosalyn.He loves me
你知 我知 他知
You know it,I know it,He knows it
已经结束了 接受现实吧
It maybe done now
It was beautiful and it was real
我们爱着彼此
- 闭嘴
And  we loved each other
- Shut up!
你恐吓他 控制他
You scared him  you manipulate him
还利用你的儿子
And  you use your son!
他肯定还爱着我 他心里还有我
Well  he must like it on some level
He must want it
因为他还一直回来
Because  he keeps coming back for it
就像你喜欢某种香水的味道
It's like that perfume that you love
情不自禁地想闻 哪怕已经发酸了
You can't stop smelling
Even when there's something sour in it
欲罢不能
Can't get enough of it
你猜怎么着 他离不开我
But  guess what?
He's never gonna leave me
他总是很渴望我
He is always going to want me
我会让你后悔的 伊迪丝
And I will make you so sorry Edith
你对我家庭的所作所为 我会让你付出代价
I will make you so sorry
for what you've done to my family
你给我记好了
Mark my words!
你他妈的糟糕透顶
That's fucked up!
我从没这样形容过别人
I would never say
anything that's fucked up
除了你
因为你从内而外让人作呕
to anybody  But  you did
B'cos you're gross inside
你才让人作呕
Oh  I'm gross inside?
Maybe  your gross inside
坑蒙拐骗无恶不作
both robbing people
and all that shit that you do
也许我们都是烂人
要不欧文怎么会看上我们呢
Maybe  we are both gross inside
That's what Irving loves about us
他这点倒是始终如一
At least  he is consistant
你人生中的一切
You know sometimes in life
all you have
都糟糕透顶 全是最坏的选择
are fucked up
poisonous choices
女士们先生们 我们的朋友
Ladies and gentlemen
Our friend
同事 我的朋友
working men friend
My friend
市长卡迈因· 鲍里托!
Mayor Carmine Polito!
你好 卡姆登
Hello  Camden
你好 新泽西
Hello  New Jersey
你好 大西洋城
Hello  Atlantic City!
很多朋友失业了
A lot of my friends
has been out of work
很多工薪家庭
A lot of good working families
只是想工作和生活
Just wanna work and live
他们说我们没钱 无处可去
They say  there's no money
no where
开玩笑
You gotta be kidding me!
是我们建设了这个国家
Don't they know
we build this country!
在新泽西 有件事可以肯定
One thing we can all afree upon
in the state of New Jersey
那就是我们永不放弃 对不对
is that  we never;
never ever give up  Do we?!
对
- NO!!!
让我们一同举杯
Please  raise your glass with me
敬新时代
To a new era
将在今晚拉开序幕
It begins tonight
我和我的家庭
From me  and my family
向大家表示感谢
We thank you
因为你们的辛勤劳动
For all the hard work that
you have given us
你们为社会
In the community
所作出的贡献
非常美好
Look what you've done
It's beautiful!
谢谢大家
Thank You!
伊迪丝?
Edith?
用下你的电话
Can I use your phone?
昨晚真是太疯狂了 我都搞清楚了
Last night was insane I got it all figured out
斯托达德·托尔森
Stauton Thorson?
听着 帮我订下广场酒店的谢尔曼套房
Listen  I need the Sherman suite
at the Plaza Hotel  Okay?
那可是整整一层楼
That's the whole floor of the hotel
我要的就是一层楼
No  no  no
I need the whole floor
行动需要
I need it for my operation
别再说什么行动了理查德
Stop calling it your operation  Richard
这不是行动需要
It's not you operation and
我不会给你在广场酒店包下一层楼
I'm not giving you a whole floor of the Plaza Hotel
议员很快就要到
I have members of the congress
coming in right now
帮酋长办美国国籍
trying to get the Sheikh
Citizenship  alright?
他们受贿了
They are taking bribes
马上就要开始
It's happening right now
马上
That's happening right now!
行贿国会议员
你他妈疯了吗
Bribing members of congress
Are you out of your fucking mind?
斯托达德  斯托达德 闭嘴
Stauton  Stauton! Shut up!
你知道维克托·特莱吉奥是谁吗
You know who Victor Tellegio
维克托·特莱吉奥
Victor Tellegio
梅耶·兰斯基的手下
你知道他是谁吗
works for Meyer Lansky
You know who that is?
国际度假村
Resorts international
他要一千万 只给我两周时间
Alright? He wants 10 million dollars
I have two weeks  I have
听我说 听我说
Just listen to me  Listen to me
你根本就没在听
You're not listening to me!
只有两周
I have two weeks!
两周搞定一切
I have two weeks to put this
thing together
我要你给我在广场酒店包下一层
And  I need you to get me the Sheman
Suite at the Plaza Hotel!
别那么激动
- 我他妈怎么能不激动
Lower your voice
- How the fuck am I doing
帮我冷静下来 伊迪丝
Calm me down Edith
帮我冷静一下
Calm me down
让我冷静下来
You gotta calm me down
冷静下来
宝贝 现在就做爱吧
Baby  let's do this right now
不 不
- 我现在就想要
No  no  no
- I wanna do this right now
看看你的脸
天
Look at your skin
Oh  my god!
你的脸滚烫 宝贝
Your fucking skin is glowing  baby
火热滚烫
Your fucking skin is glowing
不行 还没到时候
We are not gonna go all the way until we do it for real
我现在就要做
I wanna do it right now!
我们有约在先的
That's what we agreed on  alright
现在不行
So  we're not gonna do that  alright?
清醒一下
Where are you?
你吓坏了
听到了吗
You're acting all scared
You okay? You're here with me?
我爱你
I love you
我是认真的 我说了
It is real now  I just
I just said it
现在可以了
So  now is the time
看着我 我爱你
Look at me  look at me
I love you
我爱你
我说出口了
I just said that
想来真的吗 想知道真相吗
Do you wanna the truth?you wanna the real?
我准备好了
I'm ready for real
这才是真的 听到我的声音了吗
This is real,Do you hear my voice?
这是真的
This is real
你现在听到的才是真的
This is real,what you hear is real.
什么
What?
这才是真正的我
- 什么意思
This is me
- What do you mean?
口音怎么变了
Well  you're doing an accent?
怎么变成美国口音了
- 我不是英国人
Your american accent?
- No  there's no english
地地道道的美国人
There's only American
There's no English
你说什么
What are you talking about?
你是伊迪丝 伊迪丝·格林斯雷
Stop it,you are Edith,Edith Greensly
不是皇室 但你是英国人 我查过你的档案
Not royal, but you're British.I checked your records.
档案是伪造的
I falsified my records back to birth
I falsified them
我叫西德妮·普罗塞 来自新墨西哥州 阿尔布开克
My name is Sydney Prosser
I am from Albuqurque  New Mexico
我不是伊迪丝·格林斯雷 根本没有伊迪丝这个人
I'm not Edith Greensly
There is no Edith Greensly
你吓到我了
You're  freaking  me out
你在厕所时说过
No  you said it in the stall
我们要彼此坦诚
That we are gonna be real
不再弄虚作假
And  that we aren't gonna fake it
我现在向你坦白
I'm being real now
这就是我 我是西德妮·普罗塞
This is who I am
I am Sydney Prosser
好吗
Okay?
你为什么还要装英国口音
So  why did you do an
english accent?
在那之后
After that
抱歉我在厕所没告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
in the stall
我假扮伊迪丝是为了生存
I created Edith  b'cos
I need it her to survive  Okay?
但是现在该做个了断了
But  i'm done with her now
我他妈受够了
I'm so fucking done with it
你为了生存不是也伪装吗
Right  you do what you need to survive  right?
你……
You uh
你跟你妈住一起 还有个未婚妻
你都不承认
You know  you live with your mom
You have a fiance  you don't even acknowledge
还用小卷发棒 把头发弄卷
That's what you do.
You curl your hair in little fucking curlers
还好 不难看
No it's okay
You look good with it
可你本来是直发
You know You have straight hair
这就是你为了生存做出的伪装
That's what you do to survive
我们都一样
You do all sorts of things
You know  we all do
我脑子好乱
I'm confused
好乱
- 我他妈脑子也很乱
I'm confused
- I'm fucking confused too  Alright?
我们应该来一炮
I think we should fuck
感受一下
And then  we'll feel it
就不会那么迷茫了
And then  we won't be confused anymore
再说一遍 我不想做爱
No  I wanna talk it over
I don't wanna fuck  Okay? No
这对我们有好处
I think we will be better
我不想干你
我他妈不想干你
No  I'm not fucking you
I'm not FUCKING fucking you
他妈的
Shit!
老天
Oh  my God!
请离我的伊迪丝远一点
我很客气地要求你
Will you please step away from Edith
Please? I am asking you nicely
离伊迪丝远点
Please  step away from Edith right now
快点走开
Come on  step away from her
Please?
你指的是西德妮吧
You mean  Sydney?
对不起我告诉他了
I told him  I'm sorry
我他妈什么都不在乎了
I just don't give a fuck anymore
I don't give a fuck
我他妈不在乎
I don't fucking care
欧文拿着枪 嗯
Irving with a gun  right?
里奇让我们陷入的困境比坐牢还糟糕
Where Richie has got us into
is worst than jail
我昨晚告诉过你
I told you last night
这结果并不好
Those scores weren't good
怎样 现在谁能给特莱吉奥
And  what  Now  what?
No one is getting
筹到一千万 完蛋了
Ten million for Tallegio
It's over
我不这么认为
- 什么
I don't think so
- What?
什么意思
What do you mean?
等特莱吉奥搞清楚真相
Because  when Tallegio finds out
what happens
你以为他会追杀我
You think he's gonna go after me?
这个局子里的人
Someone from the bureau
他也不会动政客一根手指
He isn't gonna go after the politicians
他要杀的是你
He's gonna kill you
还有你儿子
And  he is gonna go after your son
和西德妮
And  Sydney
斯托达德·托尔森
Stauton Thorson?
给我订谢尔曼套房
Yeah  you're gonna give me
The Sherman suite
一层楼
The whole floor
不可能 我说了 不行 你个二货
That's a no I said no whacko Jesus!
那你得跟我讲完钓鱼的故事
And  you're gonna tell me
the point of that fucking fishing story
就你这态度不行
Not the way your behaving
你有毛病吗
你在哪
What's the matter with you?
Where are you right now?
问这干嘛
What does that make a difference?
告诉我你他妈在哪里
Just tell me  where the fuck you are
61号大街的办公室
Field Office  at 61st street
我现在就去找你
I'm coming at 61st street
立刻
- 你要干什么
right now
- You're gonna do  what?
痛揍你一顿
To beat   your ass
啥
You'll do what?
你是对的
You were right
我们当时应该远走高飞
We should've gone away
当时和你一起走就好了
I wish now  i'd leave with you
本来应该走掉的 竭尽全力
We are suppose to do from
the feet up
就像你一直说的
Like you always said
本来都打算好了 只有你不想
That's how we were meant to do
Only you didn't do it like that
你不想那样做
You didn't do it like that
你一直小心谨慎
You played it safe
和罗莎琳了断必然会带来风险
So there's always danger you're gonna end up with Rosalyn
就像一艘瘫痪的飞船
in the dead space
漂浮在暗无边际的宇宙
Floating on some dead spaceship
With the furnitures and the curtains
我是你的救命稻草
你就指望着我
And  I was your lifeline out
And you were mine
不会有事的
And that was okay  You know?
真希望能让你回心转意
I wish  I could get you back
没有你我做不成
But  I can't do it without you
你明白的
You know that
来吧
Come on
你我和丹尼 像我们说的那样
Me  You and Danny
Like we said
是我说的 你从没说过
Like  I said
You never said that  I said that
我们必须挺过这关
We gotta get over
on all these guys!
迫在眉睫
That's what  we need to be thinking
about  right now
该死的
Fuck's sake
太棘手了
That's big
太他妈疯狂了
That's fucking crazy
不管怎样
Whatever it is
这一定是我们干得最成功的一回
It gotta be the best
we've ever done
迪马索探员21号深夜打电话给我
Agent DiMaso called me
late on the night of 21st
我感觉他喝醉了
I believe that he was intoxicated
他恐吓我
He threatened me
我告诉他这样做很不恰当
I told him  that this was inappropriate
我们必须尊重程序
Procedures exist for purposes that
we must respect
这是我接到迪马索打来的第三个电话
This is the third such call
that I received from Agent DiMaso
5号夜里他又打来
He called me again  on the night of the 5th
凌晨两点
At two a m
他扬言要杀了我
And  he threatened to kill me
紧接着 他要求我批准他使用
Subsequently  he demanded that I allow
him to use
广场酒店的谢尔曼套房
the Sherman Suite Plaza hotel for purposes
用于贿赂议员
of bribing member of the Congress
我很抱歉
I am so sorry!
我还没读完
I'm not finished
还有很多
There's a lot more
我对你除了极其尊敬没别的
I have nothing  but the utmost respect
for you  as my mentor --
你是我的良师益友
- 干吗关了
as my mentor  as
-What are you doing?
我只是想说几句心里话
I just wanna talk from my heart
不想录下来
I don't wanna do it on record
我感到很无助
This is just  I get vulnerable
我能接着读完吗
Can I finish my ?
能读完吗 - 当然
Can I finish my sta
- Of course  of course
就是为了这个来的
That's why we're here
我尊重你
I respect you
你字典里就没尊重这两个字
I think you do  other things besides
respect me
你要干嘛
Hey!what are you doing?
这是干什么
What are you doing?
我没法控制自己的情绪
It's just hard for me to control
my passion
我是个易怒的人
I'm a very passionate person
他在中西部的时候会冰钓
You understand this
He goes ice fishing in teh Mid-west
那是我们私底下讲的
That was told to you
in confidence
一看他就是个冰钓好手
He's an 'Ice fishing guy'
Look at him
干什么
What are you doing?
你不敢
你根本不敢开枪 放下吧
It's not you
That's not you with a gun  Stop it
我敢 我就敢
You know  it's me
It's me!
别做傻事知道吗
Don't do something
that you don't know anything about
等等 别上膛
Alright?
- Wait  wait  wait  Do not load that gun
放下枪
You drop that gun
我要给你来一发
- 不要
and then  i'm gonna hit you
- Don't  don't!
看好了 傻逼
Watch this  fucko!
那么
So
你想用谢尔曼套房
You wanna use the Sherman suite
整层
- 是的
the entire floor?
- Yes
老天
- 广场酒店
God!
- Of the Plaza Hotel
黑帮那边怎么样了 我以为你…
What happend to the mafia? I thought you
不不不 这就是他们的交汇点
No no no This is where they intersect!
两个世界的人在这里交汇
The two world
The politicians and the Mafia
一边是政客 一边是黑帮
This is where the two things intersect
维克托·特莱吉奥的人
Victor Tellegio's people
经营国际度假村
who runs resort international
- Right  right
维克托·特莱吉奥露面了
Victor Tellegio  showed his face?
是的 我就坐他旁边
Yeah  I sat with him
我还跟他出去闲逛
I hung out with him
我能抓到他和他身后的整个团伙
We can get him  We can get
his whole organisation
还能让
As well  as getting
很多议员落网
any numbers of congressemen
这才刚剥开洋葱的第一层皮
that's just peeling the first layer
of the onion
哇
Wow
你打算怎么做
How're you gonna do that?
我需要一千万美金
- 一千万
We would get ten million dollars
- Ten million dollars?
一千万
- 我们刚才谈的
Ten million dollars?!
- That's how we just
那你怎么说 你打算怎么套住他
So  what does he say
he's gonna do this for us? How are you trapping him?
他们承诺建赌场
They're gonna promise to buil casinos
逃税
Handle the skims
获得执照
Do the licensing
有什么用 录下来了吗
- You have what?
You have him on tape saying this?
没有吧
You have that  right?
No
我要你用更稳妥的方法
把维克托·特莱吉奥钓上钩
I want you to find a safer way
to get Victor Tellegio on wire
一千万不行 太冒险了
No ten million dollars  that crazy
谢谢
Thank you
即使给特莱吉奥设计也是很冒险的
Right? Even to entrap Tallegio
It's crazy  But
但是 谢尔曼套房批给你了
- 不 不
You can have the Shermen suite
- No  no
去给我抓些议员来
to go and get me some congressmen
抓受贿的议员
Go and get some congressmen
taking bribes
我这回要抓到议员
I wanna pinch us some congressmen
等你的好消息 我为你感到自豪
Okay  you come back to me I'm proud of you
谢谢你
Thank you
也谢谢斯托达德
and Stauton
没丢掉饭碗算你走运
Good luck keeping your job
by the way
别把自己玩进大牢
And  staying out of jail
也别被黑帮杀了
And  not being killed by the mob!
不然倒可以说你干得很好
But  othewise  you're doing a great job
冰钓故事的结局是什么
What's the end of the ice fishing story?
我不想告诉你
I'm not telling you
我他妈的打电话问你哥
I'm gonna call your fucking brother
我哥死了
My brother is dead!
怎么样我说对了吧
That's how it ends!
他掉进冰窟死了
He fell to through the fucking ice!
不 他不是这么死的
其他原因
NO  that's not how he dies
He die in a different way
很多年以后的事了
many years later!
我知道这很尴尬
Listen  I know it's awkward and I
只想跟你道个歉
I just wanna say  i'm sorry alright?
但是我们还是可以齐心协力
But I think  we can still
stick together and uh
把事情做完
我拿到谢尔曼套房了
still fullfil on our work in here
We got the Sherman suite
一层楼
- 对 一层
You got the whole floor?
- The whole floor  yeah
不错
- 你还好吗
That's good
- Yeah  you okay?
还好 你呢
Yeah  You?
还行
这里被砸了一下
It's alright
just got hit a little bit
眼睛有点模糊
My eye  it's a little blurry
我到药店买了眼药水
I got drops at the pharmacy.
你还好吗
- 嗯 没事
You okay?
- Yeah  i'm good
我很抱歉
- 对不起
Listen  I'm sorry
- I'm sory
对不起
I'm sorry'er
摄像头放这里
就在这
We can put camera in here
Right in here  maybe
全部都能拍下来
And  we get it all on film
不错吧
- 很好
You like it?
- We do
把花递给我
You know  give me those flowers
这儿放个花瓶
镜头在那边
We put the flower vase
You can put the camera in there
就能清楚地对准沙发 拍到议员
And then  we get a clear shot of the couch
So  we could put the congressman
主意不错
That's right
That's the idea
卡迈因很快就会进监狱
And Carmine will go to jail after
he delivers us
议员也会变成阶下囚
Congressmen  soon to be felons
欧康纳议员的电话
Representative of O'connell's on the phone!
我要接电话了 大家请出去吧
I gotta take this  you guys
Everyone out  please
太可怜了
This is sad
It's just sad!
多莉我要接电话
- 抱歉 大家都出去
Dolly  i gotta take this
- Sorry  everyone out
议员先生 最近可好
Congressman  how're you doing?
我是卡迈因
It's Carmine
听说你这周要去特兰托
Tell me  you're gonna be in Trenton
This week
我有个很棒的投资机会 想跟你谈谈
We have an amazing investment
opportunity  I'd like to discuss with you
我是联邦探员里奇·迪马索
I'm federal agent Richie DiMaso
我把7.5万美金放入这个手提箱
I placed 75 thousand dollars
in this briefcase
准备给九号选区的议员约翰·欧康纳
For representative  John O'Connel
with the 9th district
卡迈因·鲍里托与欧康纳议员有过接触
Representative O'Connel was contacted
by Carmine Polito
企图绕过法律程序
To ask  if he could obtain
a rapid citizenship
为投资方阿布杜拉酋长
through an act of congress
快速办理国籍
For one  Sheikh Abdullah--
the investor
很高兴来这里
I'm excited to be here
约翰 别客气
Oh  John please
This brings the state back
我们都认识多久了
How long we've known each other?
你要帮我们的这件事
You know  what's this gonna do for us?
对新泽西有巨大的影响
This is HUGE for the state
of New Jersey
稳定经济
Stabilize our economy
酒店啦 餐厅啦 很快就会成为现实
Hotels  restaurants,Carmine sees this
It's waiting to happen
这些都他妈的快成为现实了
This fucking this is waiting to happen!
那些该死的银行家
But the goddamn bankers!
他们把钱攥得死死的
They're keeping money on the sidelines
我们拿什么去建
How're we suppose to get anything done?
除非能获得暴利
Bankers only put money in the game
银行家才肯掏钱
Where they can reap
insane profits!
先生 现在的问题是
The problem is this  Sir?
国籍
The citizenship  situation
我们必须尽快拿到 越快越好
We gotta expidite this
as soon as possible
我告诉你
你找对人了
I'll tell you
You came to the right place
可以办到
We can make it happen
务必要办到
Hey  this is going to happen
这不是开玩笑
Understand  this is real
我用我的家庭
On my family
我的孩子 我的生命和工作发誓
On my kids  On my life and my work
我了解 卡迈因
你是个好人
I know that  Carmine
You are a good man
我是联邦探员里奇·迪马索
I'm federal agent Richie DiMaso
我把7.5万美金放在这个手提箱里
I placed 75 thousand dollars
in this briefcase for one
这是为三号选区的议员杰里·桑德斯准备
representative  Jerry Sanders
of the third district
我不想做违法的事
I don't wanna do anything illegal
拜托 杰里 用它作为竞选基金
Please  Jerry
use it as a campaign donation
谢谢 这意义重大
Whatever you wanna do
- Thank you  that means a lot
我把6万美金放在手提箱里
I'm placing 60 thousand dollars into this
Briefcase for one
给第四街区Eric Keshoygan议员
Eric Keshoygan of the 4th district
我会尽我所能 卡迈因
I'm gonna do what i can
To help  Carmine
10万美金放入手提箱
A 100 thousand dollars
into this briefcase
给两届美国参议员
For two term united states Senator
新泽西的福特·里奇兰
Ford Richland of New Jersey
大西洋城
Atlantic City
一直沿着海岸线
all the way down the shore
海边的圣地
A Mecca  by the sea
卡迈因  你深受人民爱戴
你的选民
Carmine  you're beloved by your people
Your constituency
不能说是选民
It's not even a constituency
应该是你的家人
你所代表的 一个大家庭
It's your family
That's what you represent  a family
你迈出的一小步
One small thing you do for this man
是我们为新泽西人民迈出的巨大一步
It's a huge thing we do for the people of New Jersey
欧文 你要干吗
Irving  what're you doing?
你去哪
Where are you going?
上洗手间
Just gotta see a man about a toilet
抱歉
Sorry
相信我 这是我们能遇到的最大的机遇
Trust me  this is the probaby the
biggest opportunity we could have
我会竭尽所能
I'll do whatever I can in the united states
非常感谢 以我的家庭 我的孩子
I appreciate this.On my family on my kids
必须实现 一定要实现
This needs to happen
It's gotta happen
我向你保证
You have my word
我想救大家
Oh  i wanna save us
I wanna save us!
我想救卡迈因
我他妈快被折磨死了
I wanna save Carmine
It's killing me  it's fucking killing
唯一能救卡迈因的 只有通过特莱吉奥
The only way to help Carmine
is to do the Tellegio thing
风险太大了 我们必须采取行动
It's dangerous  It's dangerous
We gotta get in there
要让他见到钱 让他感到安全
We gotta get a wire in there
We gotta make him feel safe
只有一个人能搅局
There's only one thing that
could fuck this up
就是你老婆
And  that's your wife!
是的
Yeah
我不喜欢你丈夫 你们在一起不开心
I don't like your hausband
You're no better together
他从不欣赏你
He doesn't appreciate you
我的婚姻也曾是如此
But  It happens
It happened to my marriage
这就是我去迈阿密的原因
That's why I went to Miami
有时候人一定要坚强
And  sometimes you just gotta be tough
要站起来
You gotta stand up
要离开
You gotta leave  you know
有时你得学会割舍
Sometimes  you've gotta let
something die  To let  something live
你那么漂亮 却不开心
You're too beautiful  to be unhappy
我不想
I mean  I don't wanna
说我丈夫坏话 但是
bad mouth my hausband
But  just
就让我说一回吧
let me bad mouth my hausband
just for a second
他自以为无所不知
He just thinks that he knows everything
And  he's so full of shit
其实就是个满嘴谎话的骗子
He's such a liar!
他以为我蠢
但我并不蠢
He thinks that I'm stupid
But  i'm not stupid
我有次听到他们在电话里争论
I hear him on the phone  arguing
他喜欢卡迈因  讨厌其他家伙
He loves Carmine  But  he hates that
other guy
那个卷毛 国税局还是哪的
That curly headed IRS guy or whatever
在我老公旧情人面前唯唯诺诺
Who's cowering around my hausband's
ex-lover
那个红发婊子
at that  red headed whore!
反正你以后会看到的
IRS?
- Anyway  you can see that
他都抓狂了
It drives him crazy
你刚才说国税局
You said IRS
什么国税局的人
What IRS guy?
What're you talking about?
我听见他们在电话里讲的
I hear them on the phone
他好像抓住了欧文的什么把柄
I think that  he's got Irving
in some sort of bind or something
他指使欧文做事
And  he's making him do
all these sorts of stuff
欧文和卡迈因正在广场酒店
And so Irving and Carmine;
are right now are at the Plaza Hotel
把钱砸给议员还是什么人
Throwing all these money away
at like  congress or
行贿议员什么的
whatever  They're giving money
to congress or something
我不太清楚
在电话里听到的
I don't really know
But  I over heard it on the phone
真不想走
I hate doing this you
但是我要去和你丈夫谈事情
I gotta go talk to your hausband
我老板已经生气了
My boss  he's already angry
我先走
You stay here
给你钱打车回家
I'm gonna give you some money
For a taxi home
叫些甜点
Have some dessert
把起泡酒喝完
Finish the bottle of prosecco
抱歉
I'm sorry
你没事吧
You alright?
我不喜欢改变
I don't like change
真的很难受
It's really hard for me
有时我觉得到死都不能改变
Sometimes  i think that
I would die before I change
别这么说
Don't say that
没事的
你要跟我去迈阿密
It's gonna be okay
You're gonna come with me to Miami
别下手太重
Don't hurt him too bad
他还是丹尼的爸爸
He is still Danny's father
[Live and let die]
You know you did
But if this is ever changing world
In which we live in
Makes you give in and cry
Say live and let die
Live and let die
人生真荒谬
Life is ridiculous
我从来没在你面前
And  you know that
I'd never say
讲过你爹的坏话 但是
anything bad about your father
in front of you  But
你爸就是个婊子养的
Your father is a sick
son of a bitch
爸爸是婊子养的
Daddy's a sick son of a bitch?
别学我
Don't repeat that!
不过话倒没错
But  yes
罗莎琳!
Rosalyn!
我俩的关系出什么问题了
This is what's wrong
你知道我刚才在哪儿
in our relationship
You know where I was recently?
在你男朋友该死的车里
I was in your boyfriend's
fucking car
我在车上发现了你的指甲油
Alright? I saw your nail polish
我听说你的卷毛朋友是政府的人
And  what's this i hear about your curly
haired friend working for the government?
什么 谁说的 - 胡扯
What? Who said that?
你该死的老婆 -罗莎琳?
Rosalyn? -ur fucking wife!
他掏出一个帆布袋
He put a fucking canvas bag
套在我头上
over my head!
搞什么
Hey  what the fuck?!
你现在满意了吧
他想杀了我
Are you happy now?
Because  he is trying to kill me?!
你说什么啊
What are you talking about?!
你都不知道你在干什么
- 出去
What do you think  you're doing?!
- Get out of here!
你为什么不管好自己的嘴
Why are you talking so much?
会把大家都害死的
You're gonna get us all killed!
丹尼 过来宝贝
Danny Come here buddy
到旁边画画去
Go draw a picture or something
你他妈真是个婊子养的 冲我大喊大叫
You are a sick son of a bitch
for screaming at me like that
当着丹尼的面
in front of Danny
我是婊子养的
I'm a sick son of a bitch?
你差点把我害死
还反咬我
You tried to fucking get me killed
I'm a sick son of a bitch?
天
你把我逼疯了
My god!
You're driving me so fucking crazy!
你那个该死的男朋友
You're boyfriend
your fucking boyfriend
他要杀了我 还要杀丹尼
will fucking kill me
He will kill Danny
也要杀你
- 别说了
And  he will kill you
- Stop talking like that!
他是个黑手党
这是你惹上的麻烦
He's a mobster  alright
That's what you're dealing with
别说了 你不是毫发无损吗
他本可以杀了你的
Stop that! You're fine!
He'd have hurted you
你以为我什么感觉
How do you think that I feel
整天被你一个人丢在家里
All day when you leave me alone
整天  我要你做的就是爱我而已
All day! All i've ever wanted
you to do is love me
我的要求过分吗
That's all i've ever wanted
结婚就是要你爱我
That's for us to stay married
and for you to love me
我要去迈阿密
And  that's why i'm going to Miami
我要和皮特一起去迈阿密
I'm going to Miami  with Pete
I'm going to Miami  with Pete!!!
我终于找到一个爱我的人了
I finally find somebody
who loves me!
这不就是你所期望的吗
Just like you've always wanted
迈阿密太危险了 不行
Miami is too fucking dangerous!Miami  not now!
他就喜欢这样的我
He likes me just the way I am!
你给我正常点
- 你说过希望我找一个好男人
You're gonna stay normal
- You told me that you wanted to find a nice quite man!
啊 我说过
Ah  I wanted
好样的 看看你找的什么人
Doozy  you've picked
你找了个
Ohh  you hit that
最危险的家伙
the most dangerous guy  yeah
你想怎样 欧文
What'd you expect  Irving
我认识的人都是通过你的
I know everybody through you!
为什么就不替我高兴呢
Why can't you just be
happy for me?
你吃救心丸干什么欧文?
Why are you taking your
heart pill Irving?
怎么了
What's going on?
欧文  把药吃了
Irving  take your pill
你到底惹上了什么麻烦 欧文?
What kind of trouble are you in  Irving?
怎么了
What is going on?
出什么事了
What's happening?
我有个计划
I got a plan
计划 什么时候
You got a plan?When did you get it?
你知道吗
You know what?
突然灵光一闪
It really fucking came to me
就在我头被套在帆布袋里
When i was inside of that
Canvas bag
你男朋友的手掐在我脖子上时
with your boyfriend's hands around my throuat.
这时我急中生智
Yeah,that's when it really came to me
把袋子拿下来
Take the fucking bag off his head.
这周我们有两百万到帐
- 你瞧
We got two million coming this week!
- You see?
你以为这他妈是按揭啊
You think  this is a fucking
down paying plan?
我们又不是卖雪弗兰的
Are  we series of Chevrolet?
你去问维克托
You ask Victor
如果他
If he wants
这星期想要两百万 现款
two million this week
That's real money
两百万
- 现款
Two million?
- Real money
这个星期
- 怎么给
This week
- How?
转账
Wired in
是真的吗 你妻子说的 - 不是的
Is it true?
What he said about your wive?
罗莎琳说的
About Rosalyn?
我能救所有人
I can save all of us
还能存笔钱
And we can save money
照顾你和丹尼了
That'll take care of you And  Danny
好吧 但是你必须嘴巴封严
Okay? But  you gotta
close your mouth
我知道
I knew it
我经常说 你这人很难被激励
I have always said  Irving
That you're very very hard
To motivate properly
我明白了
And  I knew
皮特把你脑袋里的潜能都激发出来了
that Pete was gonna go over there
and knock some sense into your head
我刚读完这本书 欧文
I've been reading this book  Irving
韦恩·戴尔写的
《意念的力量》
It's by Wayne Dyer  that's the
"Power of intention"
我用意念把皮特传送到你那里
And  my intention
in setting Pete over to you
这样你就能想出计划来了
Was so that
you could come up with this plan
所以 不用谢
So  you're welcome
谢谢你 罗莎琳
Thank you  Rosalyn
谢谢你的计划
- 不客气
Thank you for the plan
- You're welcome
我很感激
I appreciate that
那么
So  uh
我们应该好好合作
We should be partners on this
我可是个好搭档 比伊迪丝强多了
Yeah  i'm a good partner
I'm almost better then Edith
你想过没有
也许你低估我了
You ever think about that?
You might've under estimated me?
那我们的计划是什么
So  what is our plan?
跟我说说
Tell me the plan
你会怎么做
What are you gonna do?
我会把嘴闭上 什么都不说
I'm gonna keep my mouth shut
I'm not gonna say anything
要是皮特打电话来我该怎么说
But  what do I do
if Pete calls me  What am I supposed say?
不要提政府探员
You gotta stop talking about
any government agencies
国税局和逃税什么的都不要提
the IRS and tax conspiracies
and all of that
你就说 你弄错了
You're gonna say  how you're wrong
是你弄错了
You were wrong about that
我告诉皮特是我搞错了
I'll tell Pete  that I was wrong
可是事实上
But  you know that in real life
我说的都是对的
I was right for saying that stuff
要不是我 你怎么能想出计划来的
Because that spurt on the actions
that made you come up with this plan
我会告诉皮特
- 好
So  i will tell Pete
- Okay
意念的力量 欧文
The Power of Intention  Irving
意念的力量
The Power of Intention
好的
Okay
你是对的
You are right
- Irv?
好样的
Good job peaches
欧文
Irving
我思考了很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking
你需要成长起来
You need to grow up
面对现实
And  you need to face the facts
我觉得如果离婚
And  i think that both of us
will be a lot happier
你我都会更快乐些
if we get a divorce
好的
Okay
考虑一下吧
Just think about it
说出来不容易
These things are never easy
好
Alright
欧文
Irving?
祝你的计划顺利
Good luck  with your plan
需要的确是发明之母
Necessity  truly is
the mother of invention
FBI愿意转两百万
The FBI was willing to
wirethe two million dollars
拿下特莱吉奥和他的整个犯罪集团
If it meant  taking down Tellegio
and his entire organisation
特莱吉奥这样的黑手党从不去广场酒店
Mobster like Tellegio
would never meet at the Plaza Hotel
除了他代理人的办公室
But only at the office of his attorney
阿方索·西蒙
Alphonse Simone
我是阿方索·西蒙 - 伊迪丝·格林斯雷
- Edith Greensly
Hi  Alphonse Simone
阿方索·西蒙
Alphonse Simone
请坐
Please  have a seat
我明白
I appreciate the fact that
你们都是亲自来的
You all came in person
但是完全没必要来三个人
But the trip was really unnecessary
因为只要一个简单的转账就行了
Because  this whole thing could've
been done with a simple wire transfer
事实上
As a matter of fact
这是帐号
This is the number on the wire
right here
特莱吉奥先生在哪
Where is Mr Tellegio?
很不巧 特莱吉奥先生出城做生意去了
Mr Tellegio  was unfortunately
called out of town  on business
这不行啊
Oh  that's not good
我们今天亲自来见特莱吉奥先生
We're willing to come here today
In person  to Mr Tellegio
以示尊敬
As a sign of respect
为这次的合作
- 我向你保证
To give two million dollars
- I can assure you that
我有授权书
- 不好意思能让我把话说完吗
i have power of attorney
- Excuse me  if you let me finish
我们今天愿意
We are willing
拿出这二百万
to give two million dollars today
on the temp
但是特莱吉奥先生不在
But without Mr Tellegio here
我们不能擅作主张
We can't make that decision
你没权利做这种决定
You don't have the authorisation
to make this kind of choice
别太仓促
So  don't be hasty alright?
我没有
I'm not being hasty
聪明点 好吗
Let's be smart about this  Alright?
我们不能这样做生意
This is not how we do business
抱歉
I'm sorry
我们应该在这里等下去
I think we should hang in there  alright?
等什么
那家伙又不在这儿
For what?
The guy is not here
就这样吧
抱歉 不能成交
That's it
Sorry  I can't do it!
真是个惊喜
酋长不喜欢这样
This is a surprise that
the Sheikh don't like surprises
别走
Don't leave!
伊迪丝 不能这样做决定的
Edith  this is not the way
that decision are made
我了解 能给酋长打电话吗
No  I understand but
maybe we can call the Sheikh
给酋长个打电话
Let's call the Sheikh
计划不是这样
It's not the plan
我给酋长打电话
能用下你的电话吗
I'll call the Sheikh
Can i use your phone?
请便
Please  do
打电话之前
我要再次确认
But  before I do
I'd like to go over  SPECIFICALLY
这笔钱的用途
what this money would be used for
好 在此向各位保证
Okay  What we will do
is we guarantee
任何一家赌场酒店的
All proper licenses and contruction permits
执照和建筑许可都能到位
For any Hotel Casino
计划年内营业
That is planned to open before
the end of year
然后我们就按照惯例
And  we'll throw in the customary
执行保护权
Previleges of protection
遇到阻碍怎么办
What if there's obstacles?
你们会怎么做
What will you do
- Obstacles
任何阻碍都会被克服
We are prepared to overcome
any obstacles
这可不是一般的事业
But  this is a big enterprise
如果要花钱摆平 那就花钱
If we've to pay somebody off We'll pay somebody off
如果要恐吓某人
If we have to lean on somebody
那就恐吓
We'll intimidate somebody
我们很有经验
We are experienced!
这是我们的事业
This is our business
很厉害
That's poweful stuffs
谢谢你
- 我还要告诉你一些事
Thank you
- And  I'll tell you something else
最后
At the end of this
我们会教你逃税 削减开支
We'll teach you  how to skim
And  how to cut it up
从中获利
And  make some money
on the side
因为逃税就是我们发明的
Because we invented skimming
我们都干了三十年了
We've been doing it for
thirty years!
谢谢你
谢谢你解释得那么清楚
Thank you
Thank you  for clarifying that
好的
Okay
我很满意
I'm very happy
我想酋长也会对此很满意
I think that
that will be okay for the Sheikh
我是酋长
- 特莱吉奥先生不在
This is the Sheikh
- Mr Tellegio  is not here
只有他的律师阿方索·西蒙先生
It's just Mr Alphose Simone
his lawyer
可以把钱打过去吗
Are we still okay
to wire the money?
没问题 帐号多少
Simone can take the wire
What's the number?
531……
78P  78P  76  76
转账完毕
The funds have transfered
资金已到位
The money has been wired
成交了
I think  we have a deal
合作愉快
Pleasure doing business with you
非常感谢你 西蒙先生
Okay  thank you very much
Mr Simone
谢谢你
- 酋长很高兴
Well  thank you
- The Sheikh is very excited
我们还会见面的
I'm sure we'll be seeing each other
嗯 用不了多久
Oh  I'm sure that we'll be seeing each other
非常期待
- 我也是
I'm looking forward to it
- So  am I
你也许很厌烦我
You might get sick of me
还有这两人
Like these two
我不这么觉得
I don't think I'll get sick of you
非常感谢
Thank you very much
再见 很高兴见你们
Goodbye  nice meeting you
成功了
It happened!
终于成功了
Finally!
终于抓到了
Finally  we get someone in the bag
因为我们有野心
We're ambitious.That'why.
等一下
Oh  oh  oh!
Wait  wait  wait?
如果要用钱摆平
那就花钱
If we've to pay somebody off
We'll pay somebody off
如果要恐吓某人
If we have to lean on somebody
那就恐吓
intimidate somebody
恐吓
INTIMIDATE!
必须要走这一步
Yeah  but I gotta do it
什么意思
What do you mean
没有酋长是什么意思
there is no Sheikh?
What does that mean?
没有酋长
There is no Sheikh
我要像个男人一样面对你
I wanna face you like a man
对你坦白
cos  I wanna be real now
好吗
- 那个人是谁
Alright?
- Who's the man?
那些人又是谁
Who is they?
是警察
That he's the fence
警察
- 对
A fence?
- Yeah
欧文
Irving
我是个好人
look  i'm a good person
没错
You are a good person
我从政二十年了
I've been doing this for a long time
For twenty years!
要不是为了做好事
Do you think
I would've taken that money
我会拿那笔钱吗
If it wasn't the right
thing to do?
嗯 听我说
- 哈
Now  look
- Huh?
你是个好人
You're a good person
我明白 说实话
I know that  but in all honesty
是你说的 那是唯一的出路
You said that was the only way Irv
你跑出来追我 忘了吗
You chased me  you remember?
他们逼我的
They fucking made me do it
不然就得坐牢
I was asked to do that or sit in jail
是你引我回广场酒店
You made me go back to the plaza
要那笔钱的
你个混账
To take that money
You piece of shit!
我本来已经走了
I was gone!
你个混账
操你妈
You fucking prick!
You motherfucker!!!
你他妈追我出来
人渣
You fucking chased me
you piece of shit!
卡迈因
- 我本来都走了
Carmine?
- I was gone! I left
没事吧
- 拜托 多莉 上楼
Everything all right
- Please  Dolly  Just go upstairs
好
- 带孩子上楼
Alright
- Take the kid and go upstairs
快去
- 好的好的
Please  please just go
- Of course
我会把一切解决好的
I'll make this right
我来这里就是要弥补
I came here  because
I wanna make it right
看着我
Look at my face
我像不像在撒谎
You tell me that I'm lying to you
当我告诉你 我所做的一切
When i say that  everything i do
is
都是为了新泽西人民的利益
for the good of the people of New Jersey
每一件事
Everything  I do
都是为了他们
Is for them
我像在说谎吗
Am I lying to you?
我从没交过你这样的朋友
I never had a friend like you before
我要用钱建他妈的赌场
I used that money
for that goddamn casino
我还有点手段 好吗
I got some fucking leverage  alright?
救你出来
I can help you out
都是废话 胡扯
This is all shit
This is all bullshit
看看这个
Look at this thing
看看
Look at this
什么他妈的礼仪 就是个狗屁玩具
Ceremonial fucking knife
What is this  bullshit  Some toy?
卡迈因  西德妮和我有个计划
- 出去
Carmine  Syd and I got a plan for you
- Get out
我们能救你
We can help you out
从我家滚出去 欧文
Please get out of my house  Irving
请离开我家行吗
我很客气的请你离开
Will you please leave
I'm asking you nicely  please leave
快点滚
Get out of my house  go!
滚
Get out of our house!
该死
对不起 对不起
Oh  fuck!
I'm sorry   i'm sorry
我不想事情变成这样
I don't mean for this to happen
我最在意的一切 都被你毁了
This is what matters to me most
And  you're crushing that
你要让我离开家人
You're gonna take me away from them?
我没想过事情会变成这样
I didn't wanna have this to
happen ever
你他妈婊子养的
Fucking son of a bitch!
婊子养的
You son of a bitch!
我只是想弥补
I just wanna make it right
滚出我家
Just get out of my house
看我被你害成什么样了 走吧
Look what you made me do
Pleae go
对不起卡迈因
I'm sorry Carmine
滚出去  快滚
Get out of here!
Get out!
不 卡迈因 到底是怎么了
No  Carmine   what's happening?
天哪 不
Oh  My God!
No!
操
- 欧文!
Oh  fuck
- Irving!
欧文 你没事吧
Irving  are you all right?
救心丸呢
Where're your heart pills?
救心丸在哪里
Where are your heart pills?
吃下去
There you go
起来
Okay  come on
我得躺会儿
I gotta lie down
休息一下
Just rest
准备好了吗
You ready?
是
Yeah
请坐
Please.Come and sit down
你知道那两百万在哪儿吗
You know where
the two million dollars is?
两百万
Two million?
不是给维克托·特莱吉奥
With uh  Victor Tellegio
和阿方索·西蒙了吗
and Alphonse Simone
不 事实上不在
No  actually
it's not with
维克托·特莱吉奥和阿方索·西蒙手里
Victor Tellegio or Alphonse Simone
他一定知道在哪
He fucking knows about it
钱不见了
It's gone missing
你知道吗
Did you know that?
我根本不知道 钱在哪
I know nothing about that
Where is it gone?
你这样说就有意思了
That's interesting
you would say that  Because
你们往这边来的时候
While you're on your way
over here
我们接到一个匿名电话
we got an annonymous phone call
某个人打来
from someone
他说
Who said that
作为交换
in exchange
给你们俩免罪
for immunity for the two of you
给卡迈因·鲍里托减刑
And  reduced sentence
for Carmine Polito
两百万就还给我们
We'll get our two million dollars back
真有意思
太有意思了
That's interesting
That's very interesting
我不知道
I have no idea
不知道
- 根本不知道
No  idea why?
- Not  what you're talking about
我明白了是怎么一回事了
I understand how these deals are made,right?
看到没 这家伙真有手段
See  someone has leverage
安东尼 去他妈的 结束了
Anthony  fuck them
Fuck them  it's over!
抓到他们诈骗了 结束了 你们两个都完蛋了
We got them or wire fraught
It's over  you're both done!
我不那么认为
- 你不认为
I don't think so  i don't think so
- Oh  you don't think so?
理查德 是你要求拿两百万的
Richard  you requested the two million
是你给了布兰达银行帐号
And  you gave Brenda
the account number
我们根本没插手
We didn't do any of that
一件都没有
None of it
我们怎么知道 钱不是你吞的
How do we know that
You don't have the money?
我他妈是在做噩梦吗
Am I living in a fucking nightmare  right now?
我觉得这有点冒犯
I find this a little offensive
真的有点冒犯
Really  I find this a little offensive
我看不出你这人哪里可靠
I don't see that you got any sort of cock-solid case here at all.
听我说 我们面对的是一个非常聪明的家伙
Listen to me   we're dealing with
a very clever individual
理查德
Richard
考虑一下
Think about it  alright?
你逮捕了不少人
You had some big arrest
国会议员 这能让你出名
Yeah  U S congressmen You'll look good
到处都会有你的新闻
You're gonna be all over the news
你知道不光彩的是什么吗
You know what doesn't look good?
渎职
Story about gross incompetence
我有逮捕令
I have a warrant for
不好意思 我走错房间了吗
sorry  do i have the wrong office?
不是701
This is 701  ?
阿方索·西蒙?
- 是701
Alphonse Simone?
- This is 701
我叫罗杰·西格彭
My name is Roger Thickwen
我在这里工作25年了
I've had this office for 25 years
离婚案律师
I'm a divorce attorney
你弄丢了纳税人的两百万
You lost 2 million dollars
of taxpayer money?
因为你没搞清楚特莱吉奥律师的地点和身份
Because  you're confused
about the location and the identity
of Victor Tellegio's attorney?
特莱吉奥律师阿方索·西蒙这个角色
The role of Tellegio's attorney
是由我的朋友 艾德·马龙扮演的
Alphonse Simone was played by our friend Ed Malone
长岛的冷切大王
The cold cut king of Long Island
我和西德妮第一次相遇
Whose party  we were at
就是在他的派对上
When Sydney and I first met
阿方索·西蒙
Alphonse Simone
人们总是相信他们愿意相信的 里奇
People believe what
they wanna believe  Richie
因为你们设计我 这才是原因
No  b'cos you conned me
That's why  Because
你们他妈的骗我
fucking conned me
You did
这话听起来也不太好
That  that doesn't sound
so good either
你知道我的意思
Right there
You know what i mean
我根本不明白你在讲什么
I don't know
what you're talking about
我们就假设一下
But  let's just assume
这就是你想要的故事
You wanna go with that story
真的吗
Really?
这就是你想要的故事
That's the story  you wanna go with?
这就是你想告诉纽约时报记者的
Alright? That's what
you want the New York Times to hear
你被一个骗子
That  you got conned
给骗了
By the very con men
而这个骗子
Who you 'forced'
就是当初被你逼迫
to entrap the members of congress
给议员设陷阱的那个人
In the first place
这就是你想要的
That's what you wanna go with
听起来可不太精妙啊
That doesn't sound so good
for your whole thing
是吧
Does it?
多么讽刺啊
How ironic
那些辛苦工作
that the ones who're
working hardest
努力想促进新泽西经济的人
To get  the economy of
New Jersey's going
却要被你逮捕
Those are the ones
you round up
为什么
Why? Why?
因为他们最容易抓
They are the easiest
to go after?
那些真正的诈骗犯呢
What about the real bullshit artists?
你连边也挨不到
You didn't even
come close to the big leagues
那些大佬 富豪
Those big guys
The money men
我要抓的就是那些人
That's what I was trying
to go after
抱歉告诉你 你一个也抓不到
I'm sorry to telling you
you got none of 'em
理查德 我觉得
You know Richard  i think uh
我们会叫你出庭作证 但是你也完了
We may call you as a witness
But  otherwise you're done
你最好还是回家吧
I think you better go home
斯托达德
Stauton
回家吧 理查德
Go on home  Richard
我们抓的这几个大人物
We took down some very big guys
都是那些
Among some who
规矩做事
They were just doing business as usual
服务社会国家的人
Helping their community  served their states
当然其中有些也不完全是好人
But  some of them knew
they had larceny in their blood
就算自己不承认
May never admitted it
一共抓到六个议员
But  in all
were Six Congressmen
一个参议员
One United States Senator
还有我的朋友 卡迈因·鲍里托
And my friend  Carmine Polito
我们把钱还了回去
We gave the two million back
卡迈因获得了减刑
So  Carmine got a reduced sentence
判了18个月
18 months
失去了与他的友谊
The lost of his friendship
这一辈子都是我的心结
will haunt me for the rest of my life
当事情被报道出来
When the story was written
里奇·迪马索的名字
Richie DiMaso's name
没有被提及
was never mentioned
西德妮和我住在了一起
Syd and I we moved in together
至于罗莎琳
Rosalyn
车磕碰了一下 我又不怎么灵活
The car is a little dinged up
I'm a little stiff
别再提这事了
Whatever  I don't wanna talk
about it
她一直都那么有趣
She will always be interesting
我老板知道你帮了他
You know  my boss
knows you did him a solid
是的
Yes  I did
他没拿到一分钱 所以警察没证据抓他
He never took a nickel,so they can't get him for nothing.
我不会让那种事发生的
I was never gona let that happen
欧文
Irv?
我再也不用这种指甲油了
I'm done with that nail finish
下周见
Bye for now
I'll see ya next weekend
嘿 瞧瞧你
Hey.Look at you.
鼻子上是你妈弄的吧 我帮你擦掉好吗
I think your mom got your nose.Is it ok I wipe that?
我们的诈骗生涯已被抛在脑后
Our Conning days
Were behind us
你可以愚弄自己那么久
You can fool yourself
for just so long
当你再一次改变自己时
Then  you're next re-invention
最好脚踏实地
better have your damn feet on the ground
我们从银行贷款 开一家合法的画廊
We got a loan from a bank
And  we're able to go a gellary legitimate
生存的艺术
The art of survival
是个永无止境的故事
is a story that never ends
个人原创
严禁剽窃